<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>tag:www.jobsatosu.com,2005:/all_jobs</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/all_jobs.atom"/>
  <title>Ohio State University: All Jobs</title>
  <updated>2014-02-25T10:33:00-05:00</updated>
  <entry>
    <id>53012</id>
    <published>2014-02-25T10:37:17-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-25T10:37:17-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53012"/>
    <title>Post Doctoral Researcher</title>
    <content>The Post-Doctoral Researcher will independently perform all aspects of an assigned research project(s) centered on questions regarding the mechanisms modulating ocular morphogenesis during embryonic development; responsible for design and execution of experiments, recording of experimental progress, collection and interpretation of data, maintenance of mouse lines, and production of research reports and manuscripts for publication; presentation of research progress at regular lab meetings and other university organizations; attendance and presentation at scientific conferences; guidance and support of laboratory research staff; monitoring and maintaining laboratory reagents, equipment and cell lines as assigned; initiating collaborative efforts with internal and external researchers as appropriate; preparation of training grant applications and undertaking any other relevant duties for laboratory research as assigned by the principal investigator.  </content>
    <author>
      <name>Optometry</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53052</id>
    <published>2014-02-28T16:51:53-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-28T16:51:53-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53052"/>
    <title>Human Resource Specialist</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;The Organization&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Office of Human Resources is composed of around 150 staff members who serve the University’s employees daily. This is a collaborative environment where teamwork and the sharing of ideas are vital. Our vision is to create an engaging employee experience grounded in a culture of wellbeing and optimal performance.
The Affirmative Action Specialist will report directly to the Associate Vice President of Human Resources Compliance, Risk Management, Policies &amp; Procedures. Other members of the team include individuals responsible for Employee and Labor Relations, Compliance and Policy. This is a small, collaborative team that works together to provide proactive, strategic consulting to the University.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Opportunity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This role will be responsible for the effective coordination and management of OSU’s Affirmative Action program.  This involves program administration, audit administration, outreach to key internal and external partners and project management. The individual in this role will serve as a subject matter expert to HR business partners, leaders and employees on Affirmative Action. This is a new role for the University and is a phenomenal opportunity for an experienced individual to come in and have an immediate impact.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Performance Objectives&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;•&lt;b&gt;Affirmative Action Plans:&lt;/b&gt;  Develop and implement affirmative action plans for OSU.  Partner with HR Business Partners and University leadership to review Affirmative Action Plans, identify areas for improvement and report on progress.  This individual will design solutions, develop and implement processes to achieve Affirmative Action and other HR Compliance objectives, providing sophisticated solutions to a range of internal customers. The individual in this role will be reactive to specific business needs, as well as proactive in terms of improving data flow and the development of key metrics. This position will engage in root-cause analysis and process improvement to resolve problems and enhance the Affirmative Action function.  This individual will also deliver and support the training of Recruiting, HR and managers on the Affirmative Action process, lead the development and deployment of proactive strategies, policies and programs to build a diverse, discrimination-free workplace, reinforce University values, and help drive achievement of objectives. This position is responsible for creating reports used by leadership for strategic decision making, analyzing quantitative data for Affirmative Action planning and other DOL compliance requirements and provides reports for use by the DOL, other government agencies and University administrators.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
•&lt;b&gt;Contract Requirements:&lt;/b&gt; Develop and implement additional EEO contract requirements, including periodic reviews of HR policies and works with key stakeholders for the creation of new policies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
•&lt;b&gt;Audits:&lt;/b&gt;  Serve as the key liaison between the University and government agencies.  Respond to audit requests made by the OFCCP and periodically conducts internal audits to evaluate AAP compliance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
•&lt;b&gt;Projects:&lt;/b&gt;  Accountable for contributing new ideas and innovative thinking in identifying solutions.  The individual in this role will be responsible for monitoring regulatory changes and proactively responding to changes in the environment.

</content>
    <author>
      <name>Organization &amp; HR Consulting</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53005</id>
    <published>2014-02-24T11:17:49-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-24T11:17:49-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53005"/>
    <title>Director-00</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/b&gt;
The Ohio State University, one of the nation’s leading public universities, is seeking applications for the position of Compliance Director and Title IX/Clery Act Coordinator in the Office of University Compliance and Integrity.  With the vision of supporting a university philosophy that values compliance and integrity, the Compliance Director and Title IX/Clery Act Coordinator will support a centralized compliance function that will be a leading model in higher education.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Reporting to the Assistant Vice President of Compliance Operations and Investigations, the Compliance Director is responsible for coordinating and monitoring Title IX and Clery Act compliance efforts across the university.  The Compliance Director reviews and makes recommendations regarding university policies to ensure Title IX and Clery Act compliance; develops and delivers related training; manages Ohio State’s Title IX website; participates in various university committees; prepares annual statistical reports and provides updates, interpretation, guidance, and recommendations to the Assistant Vice President of Compliance Operations and Investigations, the Vice President and Chief Compliance Officer, and other university stakeholders. The Compliance Director collaborates with various offices and areas of campus to ensure compliance with Title IX and the Clery Act.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;b&gt;For more information about the University’s Title IX program, please visit:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
http://titleix.osu.edu&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;For more information about the University’s compliance with the Jeanne Clery Disclosure of Campus Security Policy and Campus Crime Statistics Act, as amended by the Higher Education Opportunity Act, please visit:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
http://www.ps.ohio-state.edu/campus_safety/Annual_Security_Fire_Safety_Report.pdf&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Duties:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as the principle coordinator for university policies, procedures, and programs relating to compliance with Title IX, including monitoring Title IX investigations.   
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate university main campus and regional campus reporting, documentation, policies, and procedures in compliance with &lt;li&gt;Establish and document training and educational programs for the university community related to compliance with Title IX and the Clery Act.
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with local police, university police, and other university departments and offices to create and maintain crime and fire incident reports as required under Title IX and the Clery Act.
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with university departments to ensure compliance with the emergency notification requirements of the Clery Act.&lt;/ul&gt;


</content>
    <author>
      <name>Compliance Office</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53015</id>
    <published>2014-02-26T10:11:01-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-26T10:11:01-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53015"/>
    <title>Nursing Program Manager</title>
    <content>Coordinates walk-in and telephone inquiries from students about health problems; advises and facilitates preparing students for visit, gives pre-visit instructions, verifies eligibility, assists in scheduling, and refers to outside facilities in consultation with nursing management and physicians when indicated; receives telephone and walk-in inquiries from patients requesting medical care and advice; assesses need for services, offers home care advice when appropriate and supports activities of clinical service areas through communication; daily supervision of appointment associate staff; daily supervision of schedule coordination for multiple providers in various disciplines.  </content>
    <author>
      <name>Primary Healthcare</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52880</id>
    <published>2014-02-17T10:09:19-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-17T10:09:19-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52880"/>
    <title>Dean</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Introduction&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The Ohio State University seeks a new dean/director for its regional campus in Lima, Ohio to establish academic programs that will serve the region's workforce needs and students' career aspirations, to enrich the student experience in ways that enhance students' academic success and civic engagement, and to collaborate with the campus's co-located partner, Rhodes State College, in serving the local and regional communities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Position Overview&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The dean/director is the administrative leader of the Lima campus, has faculty status, and works collaboratively and consultatively with faculty, staff, and university administrators. The dean/director reports to the executive vice president and provost, and is responsible for performing the following duties:&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting, directing, and supporting the academic mission, educational activities and research opportunities of the campus
&lt;li&gt;Administering the campus's budget
&lt;li&gt;Fostering faculty excellence in teaching, research, and service
&lt;li&gt;Promoting a viable system of academic support services and student-life programs
&lt;li&gt;Maintaining high morale among the faculty, staff, and students
&lt;li&gt;Consulting with the Ohio State Lima Board
&lt;li&gt;Representing the Lima campus within the local and regional communities
&lt;li&gt;Reviewing faculty for promotion, tenure, and salary adjustments
&lt;li&gt;Supervising senior staff
&lt;li&gt;Approving course offerings
&lt;li&gt;Implementing and terminating degree programs 
&lt;li&gt;Developing and implementing outreach and engagement programs
&lt;li&gt;Working cooperatively with Rhodes State College, the independent institution that shares the Lima campus
&lt;li&gt;Overseeing the campus facilities
&lt;li&gt;Strategic planning &lt;li&gt;Fundraising&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Lima Campus</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52877</id>
    <published>2014-02-17T09:23:52-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-17T09:23:52-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52877"/>
    <title>Systems Analyst</title>
    <content>Works with the OCIO active directory team and should have strong written and verbal skills along with attention to detail; works with business sponsors and campus areas to understand business needs, goals and elicit requirements for development of systems and solutions for moderate to complex projects; produces functional specifications and obtains customer approval; acts as a liaison between the customer and the engineering team to determine and deliver the most effective solutions; contributes to the planning, testing and design of systems including writing documentation and creating diagrams; provides documentation and support for change management processes;  provides support for customer communication, awareness, and training.</content>
    <author>
      <name>OCIO Information/Identity Prot</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53006</id>
    <published>2014-02-24T15:04:38-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-24T15:04:38-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53006"/>
    <title>Business Manager 2</title>
    <content>Revenue Cycle Manager (RCM) directs and coordinates the overall functions of the patient revenue cycle to ensure maximization of cash flow while improving patient, medical provider and other customer relations. The RCM is responsible for the SHS operation related to patient financial services and revenue cycle including patient accounts, patient registration, billing, collections, coding, cash applications, insurance/vendor relations, and department goals.  The RCM must have extensive knowledge of third party payer operating procedures, revenue cycle and automated billing systems. The RCM is responsible for compliance with all laws, regulations, policies and procedures as well as required updates for SHS financial operations. The RCM will work collaboratively with other SHS administrative and clinical staff to execute strategic plans, implement and evaluate operational programs, processes and initiatives pertaining to capture and reimbursement of patient revenue and enhanced customer service and financial performance.</content>
    <author>
      <name>SHS Financial Operations</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53014</id>
    <published>2014-02-26T09:20:12-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-26T09:20:12-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53014"/>
    <title>Air Quality Technician 1</title>
    <content>The Air Quality Technician 1 provides general, preventive, and mechanical maintenance to assigned Student Life buildings and operations, which may include Campus Dining Operations; performs skilled installation and repair of air conditioning, refrigeration and heating, building mechanical and electrical equipment, domestic water and drainage systems; works on pneumatic and electric/electronic controls; repairs and replaces air compressors, pumps, belts, bearings, fans, motors and filters; repairs steam traps and installs piping; repairs commercial kitchen equipment; inspects and maintains life safety systems; inspects and performs preventive maintenance; may serve as functional crew leader; must be able to climb ladders and scaffolding and operate personnel lifts. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Oval Community Maintenance</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52825</id>
    <published>2014-02-14T08:22:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-14T08:22:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52825"/>
    <title>Director-A5</title>
    <content>Serves as the Chief Information Officer for the College of Engineering; duties to include defining strategy and providing leadership for central and distributed College IT staff, College IT infrastructure and architecture, including related interfaces with other university and external systems, application development, networks, outsourcing, academic, research and business unit support, reengineering business processes, and customizing solutions to support teaching, research and administration; tracks a broad range of emerging technologies to determine their maturity and applicability to the College and its educational and research mission; assesses the relative impact of emerging technology to strategic needs and interprets their meaning to senior organization leadership team; understands the College's collective IT competencies and their value to the units individually and to the College as a whole; determines long-term College IT needs and develops strategy for systems development, acquisition and integration; leads College technology planning and policy development, aligning a current knowledge and future vision of technology and systems with the College's goals; partners with College leadership and departments to provide overall leadership and strategic planning for the College's IT budget, ensuring the IT budget supports the College's strategic plan; closely partners with departmental Chairs, College leadership, various committees and internal stakeholders on strategies, planning, procurement and other areas of common interest; serves as member of the executive leadership team for the College and influences strategic decisions regarding the use of technology; and represents the College's IT interests and ambitions to the university's OCIO, as well as intramural and extramural peer organizations.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Engineering Computing Services</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52827</id>
    <published>2014-02-14T11:01:24-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-14T11:01:24-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52827"/>
    <title>Systems Developer/Engineer</title>
    <content>The Ohio Supercomputer Center (OSC) provides high-performance computing (HPC) services for The Ohio State University researchers and industrial clients. This Engineer position in the Supercomputer Systems group will provide technical expertise to design, develop and operate our large-scale HPC production environment. This engineer will develop solutions for OSC clients (including installing and upgrading software), monitor, troubleshoot and maintain HPC services and respond to emergency situations involving system problems, downtime and security breaches.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Ohio Supercomputer Center</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52775</id>
    <published>2014-02-10T11:34:26-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-10T11:34:26-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52775"/>
    <title>Coord-Recreational Sports</title>
    <content>The coordinator is responsible for planning, implementing, and assessing outdoor adventure-based courses and clinics, for the day-to-day operations of the climbing facility, and for managing the department’s outdoor equipment rental program. Implementing adventure-based programs including: instructing courses, training and developing student staff in outdoor leadership, supervising/vetting specialized instructors, setting fees for fiscal responsibility, and establishing best practices for risk management. The coordinator will collaborate with campus partners, especially academic units, to establish field-based opportunities for academic credit. Serving as a mentor for aspiring student leaders and a champion for the Office of Student Life initiatives will be over-arching themes for this position.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Rec Sports Programs</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52894</id>
    <published>2014-02-19T14:52:56-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-19T14:52:56-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52894"/>
    <title>Program Manager</title>
    <content>Manages planning and delivery activities for custom and open enrollment Executive Education programs; facilitates logistics, including scheduling of program sessions, event space and catering; manages associated program expenses through eRequest, eTravel and HR Action; coordinates with faculty for teaching assignments; works with faculty on compensation contracting and the preparation/purchasing of required session materials; provides onsite program administration (and offsite as necessary); assists with program communications, client/participant requests and financial/final reporting; serves as a liaison between Executive Education, university faculty and senior client representatives in planning the delivery of programs; facilitates additional Executive Education events and activities as needed; works occasional weekends and evenings.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Executive Education</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52786</id>
    <published>2014-02-11T16:27:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-11T16:27:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52786"/>
    <title>Program Coordinator</title>
    <content>The Special Collections Cataloging Coordinator leads a program consisting of effective and consistent processes to provide access to the diverse Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections through the library catalog and other library discovery tools; under the general direction of the Head of Special Collections Description and Access, works collaboratively with the Special Collections Processing Coordinator and curatorial staff to improve intellectual and physical control over materials described in the library catalog; facilitating the discovery and the use of these materials by researchers, and ensuring that the library can effectively manage collections; establishes policies, procedures and best practices; supervises department staff with cataloging responsibilities.</content>
    <author>
      <name>University Libraries</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52817</id>
    <published>2014-02-13T13:08:14-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-13T13:08:14-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52817"/>
    <title>Director Student Health Services</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Position Overview&lt;/b&gt;
Student Health Services’ mission is to provide accessible, high quality health services to support students’ academic success and co-curricular engagement. The Director serves as the general public health officer for the Ohio State University’s 63,934 students. Oversees and directs all services provided by Student Health Services and is responsible for insuring that those services meet the needs of students and the University at large.  This position assumes primary responsibility for the quality of care and services, oversight of compliance with all legal requirements, and accreditation standards.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Position Environment&lt;/b&gt;
This position reports to the Vice President of Student Life and works collaboratively with the directors and staff of the Counseling and Consultation Service, Student Wellness Center, Student Health Insurance and many other Student Life and University departments. This individual must form collaborations and maintain strong alliances within OSU Health Sciences.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

Within Student Health Services, this individual will primarily interact with members of the senior leadership team, medical providers and clinical support staff.  However this individual has oversight and will have regular contact with most Student Health Services’ employees. There are approximately 125 employees which staff the following areas:

&lt;b&gt;Primary Care    
Women’s Services     
Dental Services     
Optometry     
Preventive Medicine
Advice &amp; Appts  
Laboratory   
Sports Medicine &amp; PT     
Radiology     
Pharmacy    
Administration
Health Information Services     
Health Application Support    
Fiscal Support Services     
Allergy&lt;/b&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;   

This individual has a supervisory role and will directly supervise the Associate Director and Medical Director and has dual oversight of the Business Manager. Interested candidates can expect both teamwork and the robust exchange of ideas to be highly valued.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Performance Objectives&lt;/b&gt;
Specifically, this position will be responsible for:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

• Overseeing budget of $16 million.

• Acquiring an understanding of the health services revenue sources including the Student Health Insurance, third party insurance plans, general funds and other revenue enhancing programs.

• Obtaining an understanding of the health services’ business continuity plan in the event of a significant event that may adversely impact the facility.

• Overseeing the development of an organizational structure that maximizes health center resources and facilitates better access to health center services.

• Overseeing all aspects of a $7.1 million health center renovation.

• Managing public health issues such as a disease outbreak in a large institution.

• Building and establishing collaborative relationships with the directors of Student Wellness, Counseling and Consultation Service, and Student Health Insurance to insure that students have access to health care and a continuum of care across departments.

• Building and establish collaborative relationships with the leadership of the health sciences and public health colleges to improve service delivery, increase teaching opportunities for health sciences’ students and research opportunities that could improve the health and wellness of the student population.  

• Becoming proficient with the health center’s electronic health record and other health care applications. 

• Becoming a credentialed physician with privileges to provide care to health center patients.
</content>
    <author>
      <name>SHS Administration</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52650</id>
    <published>2014-02-03T14:42:24-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-03T14:42:24-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52650"/>
    <title>SR Systms Dev/Eng-Sap</title>
    <content>The Ohio Supercomputer Center (OSC) provides high-performance computing (HPC) services for university researchers and industrial clients. This Manager position in the OSC Web and Interface Applications Group will lead the specification, design and development of software applications leveraging OSC services. This covers a broad range of services including OSC OnDemand, science gateways, and industrial services like AweSim, and HPC interface apps for tablet and smartphone platforms.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Research and Development</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52874</id>
    <published>2014-02-17T08:17:17-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-17T08:17:17-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52874"/>
    <title>Senior Research Assoc-Engineer</title>
    <content>Conducts and supports research experimentation within the Gas Turbine Laboratory (GTL); conducts research activities related to advanced turbomachinery designs and participates in detailed interface discussions with technical research sponsors specifically important to industry involved in advanced engine designs and generally funded by the gas turbine industry, NASA Glenn Research Center, or Wright Patterson Air Force Base; plans experiments, analyzes data, and documents results in technical reports and archival publications to technical journals with emphasis on heat transfer, film cooling, aerodynamics, and forced response; produces facility designs, supervises detailed construction of components, and operates high-speed facilities; operates GTL high frequency digital data acquisition system; designs and calibrates instrumentation systems and miniature components for installation in gas turbine machinery; supervises undergraduate honor student projects within the GTL.    </content>
    <author>
      <name>ARC-Aerospace Rsch Center</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52545</id>
    <published>2014-01-28T12:13:38-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-01-28T12:13:38-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52545"/>
    <title>Director-00</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Transportation Research Center, Inc (TRC) Director – Performance Profile&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 
The Transportation Research Center, Inc. (TRC Inc.), the industry leader in motor vehicle testing, located 40 miles northwest of Columbus, Ohio, is searching for a new President. This is an exciting opportunity to lead the largest and most widely recognized independent vehicle testing facility in the world. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;b&gt;TRC Inc. Overview &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;

TRC Inc. independently manages the Transportation Research Center (Center), an independent research and testing facility serving the needs of industries, governments, trade associations and educational organizations worldwide. The Center, developed by the State of Ohio as a transportation research and development proving ground with the purpose of encouraging motor vehicle research and development activities, began operations in 1974. 

In 1979, the State of Ohio Transportation Research Board entered into a management agreement with The Ohio State University (OSU or University) College of Engineering to oversee operations of the Center, located on 4,500 acres in East Liberty, Ohio. In 1988, the Center’s assets were sold to Honda of America Manufacturing, Inc. (HAM) as part of an economic inducement to build a manufacturing plant in Ohio. 

After the sale, OSU created TRC Inc., a non-profit corporation. TRC Inc. and HAM entered in a management agreement for TRC Inc. to manage the Center as a multi-user facility. TRC Inc. is governed by a seven-member Board of Directors, chaired by the University’s Dean of the College of Engineering. The TRC Inc. President is also a Board member.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The Center includes 15 buildings, a 7.5 mile test track, an ATV test course, a Dynamic Handling Course, and other various vehicle testing facilities. TRC Inc. is organized into three business units – Durability &amp; Dynamics Operations, Laboratory Operations, and Contract Services. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Position Overview&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This position, reporting to the TRC Inc. Board, holds a joint appointment – to TRC Inc. (as President) and to the University (as Director). This position, managing a $50 million budget and over 370 staff, is responsible for the overall business strategy, financial performance, operations and administration, compliance, policy development and implementation, facilities management, marketing and business development, and all other responsibilities generally associated with the position of chief executive officer. This position must provide strategic and tactical leadership to ensure TRC Inc. grows and remains the leading independent provider of automotive testing, and research and development in the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt; Performance Objectives&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 Some of the key objectives, against which performance will be measured, include: 

- Lead, in collaboration with the Board, an evaluation of the strategic plan, and if necessary, restructure the business to ensure a sustainable financial model exists, and establish one that is flexible and can adapt to different economic cycles, to meet customer and stakeholder expectations and provide the expected funding to the University Endowment Portfolio to support the College of Engineering’s transportation research. 

- Evaluate the organizational structure and the skills of the leadership team, and if necessary, implement changes to ensure TRC Inc. is organized in the optimal structure and effectively resourced to execute its strategic plan. 

- Strengthen the relationship between the University, HAM, HRAO (Honda R&amp;D Americas, Inc. Ohio Center), and TRC Inc. to ensure common interests are served. 

- Develop and execute a business strategy to ensure the Center’s service offerings are relevant in the market, grow top-line revenue and net contribution, protect and grow business from major customers (e.g., HRAO and NHTSA/VRTC), and strengthen TRC’s brand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Leadership Competencies and Personal Characteristics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

The Board is searching for a visionary and strategic leader with the emotional intelligence to lead a business transformation in a complex business and governance structure. As President, the new leader must be inspiring and enjoy a high profile role to promote and advocate for the Center and its mission. 
The successful candidate must be an effective communicator, persuasive and influential, with a customer service orientation to build collegial and collaborative partnerships. He/she must also be politically savvy, with diplomacy and effective negotiation skills, to effectively promote and defend his/her position to various stakeholders. Other key leadership competencies include being a proactive and effective problem solver, creative and innovative, flexible and adaptable, and a good listener communicating in an open, honest and transparent manner.
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Engineering Experiment Station</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52788</id>
    <published>2014-02-12T09:04:31-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-12T09:04:31-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52788"/>
    <title>Director of Development</title>
    <content>The Development team in CFAES focuses on strengths in a positive work environment.  While performance metrics are key to success, the balance of the science and the art of fundraising in this position will lead to a bright future as the team is on the ground floor of building something special with unbelievable opportunities. The Director of Development provides direction and coordination of fundraising strategies for the College of Food, Agricultural, and Environmental Sciences, with emphasis on 4-H and OSU Extension; serves as a liaison with the 4-H Foundation; develops and implements short- and long-term plans to secure major gifts from alumni, friends, volunteers, corporations, foundations and other entities in support of the college's and university's missions, objectives and priorities as set by the unit directors, college dean and development's senior vice president.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Development/OSU Foundation</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52458</id>
    <published>2014-01-23T16:30:07-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-01-23T16:30:07-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52458"/>
    <title>Residence Hall Director</title>
    <content>OSU is seeking ENGAGING, COLLABORATIVE COMMUNITY BUILDERS who are committed to helping students succeed.  Are you dedicated to reaching out, leading and connecting students to Ohio State’s many opportunities, and traditions?  Our Residence Life team is comprised of professionals who are committed to building inclusive and globally aware communities, supporting student wellness, promoting student learning, and gaining a broad understanding of the student life enterprise.  

Successful candidates will have the skills to develop strong residential communities; form relationships with individual students; implementing intentional programs for first and second year students; coach and supervise Resident Advisors; mentor graduate students; coordinate learning communities and creative academic initiatives; collaborate with faculty and academic partners; shape student leaders through advising; engage in educational conduct conversations; encourage dialogue about identity and differences; provide support and referral to students; and are administratively skilled. 
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Residence Life</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52655</id>
    <published>2014-02-04T15:59:03-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-04T15:59:03-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52655"/>
    <title>Compensation Consultant</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;The Opportunity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The compensation team is a critical part of Human Resources and provides consultation services that include interpretation and use of market data, annual merit process, compensation program design, equity studies, and executive compensation.   

A thorough review and modification of the university’s large and complex compensation and classification structure Is underway. Over the next 3 years, the university will drive the effort to review and update Ohio State’s compensation and classification system. This major project will introduce consistent use of titles, improve market matches, ensure internal and external pay equity, develop competencies for each role, and provide clear career path opportunities.    

The Compensation Consultant will be a key participant in this compensation and classification project.  This is a unique opportunity to be actively involved with a dynamic project that will have an impact on over 20,000 staff members.   In addition, this position will perform compensation and classification functions which support the strategic goals of both the university and individual colleges/VP units.   This position will touch every aspect of the Compensation program and will significantly contribute to its advancement and success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Environment&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This position reports to the Manager of Compensation in the Office of Human Resources, Total Rewards Center of Excellence.   Within the Office of Human Resources, this position will interact primarily with members of the Compensation team, HR Information Technology and Data Analytics.  Other key relationships will include Field HR Generalists, Medical Center Compensation team, Payroll and external vendors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Performance Objectives&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; Specifically, this position will be responsible for:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Compensation &amp; Classification Redesign Project:&lt;/b&gt;
•	Participating as a project team member in significant project to redesign the entire compensation and classification system for the university.
•	Serving as functional lead for assigned Job Functions to develop and socialize new job family structure and associated descriptions.
•	Serving as campus lead for the implementation of new market pricing software system. 
•	Completing market pricing analysis for new jobs. Assisting in development and analysis of new market based salary structure. 
•	Contributing to the development of a career path framework.  
•	Participating in policy and procedure review and updates and organization change management and project implementation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

&lt;b&gt;On-going Compensation Administration:&lt;/b&gt;
•	Consulting with colleges and VP units and providing data-driven recommendations on effective pay strategies in order to ensure equity across departments.
•	Making determinations on reclassifications, salary adjustments, and bonus requests, and completing job analyses and job audits, all while ensuring adherence to university policies and federal &amp; state regulations.
•	Analyzing and interpreting key compensation metrics and trends, including equity and market analyses to facilitate OSU’s commitment to competitive pay.
•	Building strong working relationships with a wide variety of individuals, including HR partners, vendor consultants and colleagues.
•	Participating in developing and managing course content for HR System (PeopleSoft) courses, including instruction and facilitation; conduct system testing for HR System modules. Human resources professionals throughout the entire university are educated through these training sessions.
 </content>
    <author>
      <name>Compensation &amp; Classification</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>51977</id>
    <published>2013-12-13T13:54:31-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-12-13T13:54:31-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/51977"/>
    <title>Open Faculty Search</title>
    <content>Serves as tenure track faculty affiliated with the Center for Automotive Research (CAR) in areas related to automotive systems and sustainable mobility; builds strong collaborations with faculty across the college of engineering; actively participates in multidisciplinary teaching and research activities; works closely with the director in planning and executing strategic initiatives.  </content>
    <author>
      <name>Engineering Administration</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>51912</id>
    <published>2013-12-09T11:43:14-05:00</published>
    <updated>2013-12-09T11:43:14-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/51912"/>
    <title>Open Faculty Search</title>
    <content>Serves as tenure track faculty affiliated with the Center for Automotive Research (CAR) in areas related to automotive systems and sustainable mobility; builds strong collaborations with faculty across the college of engineering; actively participates in multidisciplinary teaching and research activities; works closely with the director in planning and executing strategic initiatives.  </content>
    <author>
      <name>Engineering Administration</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52321</id>
    <published>2014-01-13T15:10:05-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-01-13T15:10:05-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52321"/>
    <title>Senior Research Assoc-Physical</title>
    <content>Functions as a technical expert and manages the routine maintenance and calibration of the lasers and instruments involved with of time-resolved optical spectroscopy experiments within the Center for Chemical and Biophysical Dynamics (CCBD); trains and supervising graduate and undergraduate students and postdoctoral researchers associated with the Department of Chemistry and Biochemistry (CBC) and the Institute for Materials Research (IMR); aids in the acquisition, provides technical expertise in developing projects for customers internal and external to OSU including data analysis and manuscript preparation; gauges the users' ability to use the system independently and/or runs experiments for those who are not trained users; manages the operations of the CCBD providing initial diagnosis of system failures; invoicing of users and maintains records; ordering consumables; helps identify instrument upgrades; coordinates system scheduling and usage. works with faculty on drafts of proposals for new instruments and instrument upgrades; compiles CCBD's operating budget; coordinates management of CCBD with CBC Research Support Services (RSS), and IMR; acts as first contact to potential and current outside users, performs educational activities, and disseminates information about CCBD's services; attends and participates in IMR events and seminars including Materials Week conference and IMR Member of Technical Staff meetings; represents IMR and CCBD at OSU and external events; provides quarterly brief updates and annual reports on CCBD and individual activities to IMR; solicits new users; identifies needs of potential users; works with IMR to encourage multi-college and industry user base; performs other duties as assigned by supervisor.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Chemistry and Biochemistry</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>51354</id>
    <published>2013-10-29T16:13:03-04:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-29T16:13:03-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/51354"/>
    <title>Open Faculty Search</title>
    <content>The College of Optometry at The Ohio State University invites applications for a tenure-track faculty appointment. Applicants at all career levels with a PhD or equivalent are encouraged to apply. Depending on qualifications, an appointment may be made at the assistant, associate, or full professor level. Research and teaching interests may be in any aspect of vision science in the broadest sense, whether basic, clinical, or translational in approach. Significant emphasis will be placed on the potential for obtaining external funding and for contributing to the academic mission of the College.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ohio State University has the nation's most comprehensive health sciences center including the Colleges of Dentistry, Medicine, Nursing, Optometry, Pharmacy, Public Health, and Veterinary Medicine. In addition the campus houses other disciplines related to vision science including the Colleges of Biological, Mathematical and Physical Sciences; Engineering; and Social and Behavioral Sciences. Collaboration across disciplines is actively encouraged. The College of Optometry offers a collegial environment with an excellent faculty engaged in an expanding program of externally-funded research in a new research facility and has a progressive optometric professional program. A competitive salary and start-up funds are negotiable commensurate with qualifications and needs.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Optometry</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52998</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:30-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:30-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52998"/>
    <title>Line Cook</title>
    <content>Under supervision from the unit Sous Chef, the Line Cook is responsible for the preparation of all types of food including, proteins, starches, soups, sauces, stock and gravies, a la cart items, grab-n-go and cook to order style foods; operates as part of the unit culinary team; interacts and improvises dishes directly with customers often in theatrical style; interprets recipes, weighs and measures ingredients, and operates standard kitchen equipment.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Morrill Commons</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52980</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:19-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:19-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52980"/>
    <title>Delivery Worker 2</title>
    <content>Serves as an active member of a diverse Logistics and Distribution department; performs pickup, sorting and delivery functions associated with various department products, including, but not limited to: US Mail, Campus Mail, Parcels and freight items from multiple origins; operates up to 20 foot long straight truck; loads and unloads vehicles; utilizes appropriate freight moving equipment as needed; maintains delivery records; obtains signatures from customers; inspects and maintains cleanliness of vehicles; reports vehicle problems to supervisor for repair; maintains documents associated with delivery manifests, productivity cards and vehicle records.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Receiving</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52964</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52964"/>
    <title>Systems Manager - Not Sap</title>
    <content>Provides oversight, support and coordination of the College's instructional, student and research labs; provides daytime support of the FCOB instructional, student, and research labs; responsible for monitoring computer lab utilization; coordinates scheduling of events in Mason Hall rotunda and manages delivery; supervises evening computer lab manager and research lab managers; schedules, hires, trains and supervises student proctors; reports repair needs and escalates issues appropriately; coordinates maintenance and repairs and maintains inventory; reviews and processes lab suspensions; on-call manager for after-hours support and questions; develops and implements policies and procedures in consultation with Director of Operations; stays apprised of trends in technology; recommends changes to improve learning environments, and determine hardware or software requirements related to such changes; verifies PC imaging applied correctly in all instructional spaces; works with other staff to ensure proper software is included in all instructional, student, and research computer labs.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Facil &amp; Classroom Tech</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53075</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53075"/>
    <title>Coord-Planning And Scheduling</title>
    <content>The role of the Operations Planner is to improve staff productivity and work quality by anticipating and eliminating potential delays through planning and coordination of labor, parts, material, and equipment access; works with maintenance shop supervision and crew leads to develop long and short term plans for equipment repair and maintenance based on plans handed down by Facilities Operations and Development administration and corrective work initiated through the Preventive Maintenance program; works closely with the Maintenance Engineering group to improve quality of PM and planned work requests, including procedures, equipment inventories, parts lists and replacement data captured in the CMMS system; work in conjunction with the zone staff to construct daily, weekly and monthly planning schedules when workload permits; stays in coordination with stakeholder through continual communication with first line supervision, the planning group and materials coordination; collaborates with other Maintenance Planners, Maintenance Engineers, and support groups to insure standardized maintenance processes.  </content>
    <author>
      <name>Facilities Support</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52858</id>
    <published>2014-02-15T01:03:40-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-15T01:03:40-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52858"/>
    <title>Project Coordinator</title>
    <content>Founded by a collection of young and energetic OSU faculty, postdocs and staff, the STEAM Factory is a diverse and inclusive grass-roots network in the OSU community that facilitates creative and interdisciplinary collaboration, innovation and dissemination. The Project Coordinator will serve as the primary point of contact for STEAM projects and will interact with groups of faculty across multiple disciplines, managing staff and communicating both within the OSU academic community and to the public; manages STEAM project operations: duties include professional writing, grant proposals, organization of documentation, marketing, web development, program development and event logistics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;Must be available for evening and weekend meetings/events.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Manages project operations:&lt;/b&gt; Organizes, develops, and writes content for grant proposals and funding applications; plans and writes content for the STEAM Factory website and social media accounts; writes and edits publicity materials, including press releases for external publication and within OSU websites and magazines; manages various STEAM listservs and email accounts, including collating information for and writing a weekly summary update email for STEAM factory members; develops and maintains the outreach and engagement activities calendar; schedules events and meetings; assists with advertising for events; maintains contact with external partners and collaborators.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Attends STEAM meetings, held both on and off campus, to prepare minutes and plan for coordination of projects. These meetings are held two to four times a month during evening hours, and include meetings held both internally by the entire STEAM Factory group and external meetings between STEAM Factory representatives and community/business partners.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Functions as primary contact for purchasing and requisitioning of logistics for events, such as ordering food and reserving space; researches what supplies and set up plans may be needed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Attends public STEAM events, such as 400 West Rich markets, as the primary contact to oversee and run logistics thus allowing the Chair of STEAM to focus on outreach and engagement of the visiting public; establishes procedures for the production of the event; transports, maintains, sets up/takes down and photographs all market materials such as posters, electric generator, TV, etc. for STEAM events; manages student personnel/staff who provide assistance to plan and produce these events; develops training as needed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Other duties as assigned such as maintaining STEAMbase - a database to centralize information about research interests within the group and cross-disciplinary project logistics.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Mathematics</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53059</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:16-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:16-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53059"/>
    <title>Fiscal Associate</title>
    <content>This position supports the international dimension of The Ohio State University by providing support to the fiscal/procurement functions for study abroad programs in a fast-paced, deadline-driven, team-oriented environment.  Job duties include but are not limited to: accurate and timely processing of study abroad program expenditures, financial and managerial accounting for study abroad programs, financial recordkeeping and balancing of program revenues and expenditures, and program fee calculations. The fiscal associate works with faculty and staff program organizers, travel agents, and the OSU travel office to process high-volume travel procurement requests and payment requests using electronic and paper based systems in compliance with OSU policies and procedures.  Provides training to faculty and staff on expenditure policies, procedures, and recordkeeping. This position requires the use of excellent interpersonal communication skills, representing the office in a professional and courteous manner in both personal and written interactions. Requires extensive knowledge of OSU expenditure policies, travel policies, and Procurement and Group Extended Travel Card Policies. Requires advanced knowledge of MS Word and Excel and accurate and efficient data entry skills. This position also supports general office duties for the Business Operations team including but not limited to Procurement Card checkout, laptop checkout, deposits, and building coordinator.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Office of International Affair</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52957</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:00-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52957"/>
    <title>Professor</title>
    <content>Serves as Berry Chair of new technologies in marketing; develops and teaches courses designed to prepare students for careers in marketing and provides leadership in marketing programs; oversees doctoral dissertations; initiates and directs program of research in marketing strategy and management; publishes in leading marketing journals; maintains a position of national leadership in academic communities; teaching undergraduate, graduate, and Ph.D. level students; conducts research in area of expertise and serves on committees.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Marketing &amp; Logistics</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53068</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:32-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:32-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53068"/>
    <title>Traffic Control Officer</title>
    <content>As a member of the Transportation and Traffic Management team, this position is responsible for controlling vehicular and pedestrian traffic on the Columbus campus; directs traffic during roadway construction and repair, special events and other occurrences as needed; closes off road access and reroutes traffic to improve flow of vehicles and pedestrians around campus as needed for construction sites, special events or other occurrences; conducts non-injury traffic accident investigations and processes related paperwork; provides assistance and information to faculty, staff, students and visitors. Ensures motorist and pedestrian compliance with campus rules and regulations; enforces University policy regarding bicycle usage on campus; issues warnings and/or citations as necessary; removes, impounds and transports to storage bicycles as needed; monitors traffic equipment including barricades, A-frames, cones, signs, caution tape, sign stands and other materials; confirms set up/tear down of materials required for events; conducts traffic surveys; assists in training of other officers. </content>
    <author>
      <name>TTM Traffic Mgmt</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52990</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52990"/>
    <title>Research Assistant 1-B/H</title>
    <content>Provides assistance with field and laboratory research on woodland salamanders; collects data on woodland salamanders within the forest strand of southeast Ohio; collects woody and herbaceous vegetation data from field and lab experiments; identifies amphibians and plants of the region; performs analyses on forestry and wildlife vegetation to determine composition of forests within control sites; establishes and maintains plots within forest strands; keeps logs and enters data collected in laboratory and field experiments using spreadsheets; performs quality assurance checks on data and equipment.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Sch of Environ &amp; Natural Res</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52973</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52973"/>
    <title>Program Manager</title>
    <content>The Ohio State University Libraries seek a dynamic, innovative, and service-oriented individual for the position of Research Commons Manager (Program Manager) within the Research Services department. The Research Services Department provides research support to The Ohio State University community on topics and activities relevant to all aspects of the research lifecycle. Reporting to the Head of Research Services, the successful candidate will be instrumental in the planning, development and management of services for the Research Commons space. The successful candidate will also provide primary support for GIS software and services within the Research Commons.</content>
    <author>
      <name>University Libraries</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53000</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:31-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:31-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53000"/>
    <title>OSU Extension Educator</title>
    <content>The Extension Educator, Family and Consumer Sciences in Ottawa and Sandusky Counties will provide overall leadership to Family and Consumer Sciences programming targeted  to local and area needs. The Educator will also work collaboratively with the team of Extension professionals to provide Family and Consumer programming within the Erie Basin Extension Education and Research Area (EERA).Internal and external applicants are required to accurately self-disclose all criminal convictions when they apply. Final candidate offer is contingent upon the university's verification of credentials and other information required by law and/or university policies or practices based upon a criminal background check. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Ottawa County</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52982</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:22-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:22-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52982"/>
    <title>Research Specialist</title>
    <content>Serves as a specialist and technical expert for the Program of Excellence in Natural Rubber Alternatives (PENRA) and assists in the conduct of all phases of domestic natural rubber research and development efforts; supports and conducts complex experimental research in seeking domestic sources of natural rubber; coordinates PENRA reporting activities including: communicating with sponsors, gathering data among program participants, preparing summaries, and delivering reports as requested by sponsors; facilitates obtaining program equipment, materials, supplies, labor and overall program resources, manages program resources and insures that resource requests are compatible with program funds and sponsor(s) policies; conducts statistical analysis, presents program results and writes summaries, reports and publications for sponsoring agencies and a variety of audiences; coordinates PENRA program activities including but not limited to: planning and conducting experiments, purchasing equipment, developing budgets, interacting with program sponsors, insuring communication among program collaborators, identifies new funding opportunities, coordinates grant development activities, and interacts with state and federal agencies and private industry; assist in establishing and maintaining relationships with sponsors and collaborating research institutions; maintains, and makes accessible to collaborators, a comprehensive literature database on natural rubber alternatives.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Horticulture &amp; Crop Science</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52966</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:03-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:03-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52966"/>
    <title>Program Assistant</title>
    <content>Assist the webmaster with the development and maintenance of The Huntington Archive web site; design of new UI models for upgrading &amp;quot;legacy&amp;quot; sections of the existing web site; development of templates for various existing and future sections of the web site; population of pre-written content into the developed templates; and the creation of web graphics and media to accompany corresponding content. Other duties, including  but not limited to, scanning photographic film slides to digital formats, correcting imperfections in digital images, assisting with minimal database maintenance, troubleshooting issues related to web visitor experiences, updating related social media sites, and communicating with the IT department at the college level.</content>
    <author>
      <name>History of Art</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53077</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:41-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:41-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53077"/>
    <title>Head Coach</title>
    <content>Develops, directs, and coaches an intercollegiate spirit squad program.  Conducts all practices and rehearsals.  Instructs athletes in the proper technique for fundamentals of dance choreography for routines and cheerleading including tumbling, stunting, etc; responsible for the development of all routines and performances in cooperation with assistant coaches and choreographers as part of a comprehensive game atmosphere initiative; coordinates participation and performances at home football games and other sports as requested; manages requests for cheerleaders and Brutus participation in department, University, community and private events; manages all administrative aspects of the spirit squad including scheduling, travel, equipment needs, budget, and staffing; manages all college-prep clinics, cheerleader recruiting and selection process, appearances, and competitions.  Monitors academic progress of spirit squad.  Participates in development activities to promote the program.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Athletics</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53061</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:21-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:21-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53061"/>
    <title>Custodial Worker</title>
    <content>The Custodial Worker maintains a safe and clean environment in and around assigned Student Life residence halls, offices and other properties for student residents, guests and staff; responsible for day-to-day cleaning as well as other housekeeping duties involved with special housing operations; cleans rooms, offices and public areas; cleans most flat surfaces, furniture, windows, vents, and light fixtures; may count, issue, and receive linen; operates basic electrical cleaning equipment; maintains floors and carpets, moves furniture, removes trash, clears snow, and cleans building entrances and walkways; reports any damage or theft discovered in work area; may be asked to respond to emergencies; climbs ladders and scaffolding.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Housekeeping-North District</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52975</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52975"/>
    <title>Academic Counselor &amp; Staff Ast</title>
    <content>Advises current and potential Sociology and Criminology undergraduate students about academic programs, GE requirements, and career opportunities; maintains undergraduate student records; assists with evaluation of transfer credits; produces undergraduate publications, maintains Undergraduate Studies portion of website and coordinates undergraduate research; serves as liaison with other university units and undergraduate organizations, including curriculum committees; conducts orientation; teaches survey and internship courses; participates in recruitment activities; assists with commencement; possesses knowledge of all university offices/resources related to the undergraduate student experience, from admission to graduation, and makes referrals as appropriate; assists undergraduate director with curriculum, records and assessment; attends staff meetings; participates on college and administrative committees as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Sociology</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52959</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:00-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52959"/>
    <title>Senior Lecturer</title>
    <content>Teaches undergraduate and graduate students in the area of Finance; serves on committees; advises students.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Finance</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53070</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:35-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:35-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53070"/>
    <title>Director-00</title>
    <content>As a member of senior team in Administration &amp; Planning (A&amp;P), provides leadership and strategic direction for all aspects of internal and external public relations, communications and marketing efforts to support A&amp;P and its business units (TTM, FOD, PPARE, UniPrint, &amp; Public Safety); develops, coordinates and implements the communications strategy on reputational or high level public relations, public safety or crisis management issues within A&amp;P with an eye to maintaining an effective balance between broad university and A&amp;P objectives and the needs of specific departments and programs; produces detailed communications plans and serves as primary resource for executive level talking points, fact sheets and message development; responsible for the management and associated budget of the shared services unit including staffing and processes to ensure alignment with university mission and branding; ensures appropriate staffing levels and metrics associated with providing efficient and effective communications, public relations and marketing services; oversees the development  and implementation of marketing/communications plans, tools, and tactics including multimedia, website and social media strategy and development; measures and evaluates the outcomes; strategically coordinates and integrates communications efforts across A&amp;P units as appropriate; writes, edits, and develops presentations; ensures A&amp;P leaders/staff have tools needed for everyday communications; ensures A&amp;P communications, public relations and marketing efforts are integrated and aligned with university branding and communications direction and serves as liaison with University Communications and communications colleagues around the university, including strong working relationships with all areas of University Communications, Student Life, Athletics and Wexner Medical Center communications counterparts; collaborates with university media relations as needed; develops strategy and responds to media inquiries as appropriate; represents A&amp;P and advises A&amp;P leaders on public relations matters; completes and participates in other initiatives/ projects as needed.</content>
    <author>
      <name>A&amp;P Communication Services</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53054</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:13-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:13-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53054"/>
    <title>Office Admin Associate</title>
    <content>Manages and oversees daily administrative functions of the administrative office of the Center for Research &amp; Transdisciplinary Scholarship (CRTS) and provides administrative support for the Associate Dean for Research &amp; Transdisciplinary Scholarship  (ADR); coordinates the ADR's appointments and calendar; makes all travel arrangements for a variety of national and international meetings; conveys directives and information; researches and analyzes materials to aid the ADR in decision-making and planning; independently drafts, composes, and responds to correspondence; support Grants Manager with grant submissions (updating CV's, Biosketches, gathering Letters of Support, staff reminders), progress reports, and renewals; reviews and authorizes expenditures for travel, basic supplies and supplies for the biomedical labs; develops and prepares fiscal and administrative process reports; coordinates weekly CRTS meeting schedule, sets agenda, prepares minutes, coordinates follow up items with appropriate personnel; develops, organizes and oversees special projects, events, and assignments; determines and organizes agendas; prepares PowerPoint presentations and posters; assists with development and maintenance of administrative, fiscal and research databases and web-based materials; manages the solicitation and receipt of letters of support for PI grant applications; coordinates the annual T32 external advisory committee meeting.</content>
    <author>
      <name>College of Nursing</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>51353</id>
    <published>2013-10-29T12:49:18-04:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-29T12:49:18-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/51353"/>
    <title>Research Aide</title>
    <content>Under the general direction of the Dining and Residence Hall Manager and the Manager of Stone Laboratory, assists with all aspects of the Stone Lab operations with an emphasis in residence and dining hall operations; performs specific hands-on-duties related to residence and dining hall operations; assists other Stone Lab operations associates to ensure optimal operation of the residence and dining hall and develops ways to ensure quality customer service to students, faculty, staff, and guests of Stone Lab. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Center/Lake Erie Area Research</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52992</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52992"/>
    <title>Human Resources Manager</title>
    <content>Under direction of the Assistant Director for Administration and Planning, the Human Resources Manager assists leadership in talent management planning that enhances and addresses the strategic plan; leads the Libraries' Human Resources Team in executing a variety of human resources related functions including workforce planning, selection and recruitment, orientation, onboarding, exit processing, training, performance management, employee relations, policies and procedures interpretation, and assessment activities; provides distinguished customer service; plans and implements timely, efficient and accurate execution of actions and activities; resolves and follows up with problems; suggests and implements best practices; assures compliance with law, policies and procedures; completes and assures proper retention of documentation; supplies reports and statistics; serves as liaison among Library departments, Office of Academic Affairs and the Office of Human Resources.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

University Libraries employ approximately 70 faculty, 170 staff and 470 student employees in 12 locations across the Columbus campus to meet the diverse and changing information needs of the University's students, faculty, and staff, and to participate in resource sharing programs throughout Ohio and the world.
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Planning and Administration</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53063</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:26-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:26-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53063"/>
    <title>Staff Assistant</title>
    <content>Provides administrative support to the Technology Commercialization Licensing team; oversees operational and administrative functions and activities; defines and evaluates problems; initiates and gains support for improvements in new and modified program procedures; maintains internal databases and facilitates recordkeeping for licensing team marketing and company engagement; contributes to optimal business solutions and excellent customer satisfaction through effective written and verbal communication with university faculty, researchers and administrators; assists in driving licensing team portfolios through marketing processes and scheduling of companies; creates and facilitates written correspondence; liaison between Technology Commercialization office and constituents; establishes and maintains relationships with university faculty, researchers and administrators; manages high profile relationships on behalf of the Licensing team; develops correspondence, drafts presentations and prepares reports; maintains team members' schedule and calendar of events and arranges travel; responsible for significant meeting planning; ensures appropriate action is taken to meet department goals and guidelines; represents office to outside organizations, community and customer base; special projects as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Technology Licensing</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52984</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:23-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:23-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52984"/>
    <title>Office Associate</title>
    <content>Works as part of the OSU Extension team in Seneca County. The Office Associate provides general office support for all program area Extension Educators and good customer service to on-site visitors; assists with administrative/county operations for the county Extension Director and Extension Educators; and processes and maintains supply orders for program staff.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;50%:&lt;/b&gt;  General Office Support and Customer Service: Answer telephones and serve as the primary first contact for on-site visitors; provide timely and relevant information to clientele without assistance when possible through distribution of fact sheets and other resources; open, sort and distribute daily mail, fax, and other communications; prepare newsletters and other large mailings, maintain bulk mail records; operate office equipment and troubleshoot when necessary; maintain a high level of professionalism at all times and protect confidential information; create and maintain records for program registration as requested by all program area Extension Educators; maintain the 4-H membership database as requested by the 4-H Educator; and provide basic office support for all program area Educators.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;35%:&lt;/b&gt;  Administrative/County Operations: Initiate payment of all invoices through appropriate procedures; monitor and track appropriated and non-appropriated university funds, reconcile e-Reports on a monthly basis, and provide monthly reports to the County Extension Director and other Educators, prepare and make deposits, and monitor and track local account funds, reconciling on a monthly basis and providing reports to the County Extension Director and other Educators.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;10%:&lt;/b&gt;  Orders and Inventories: Maintain an office supply inventory and order items as needed; and order program related supplies as requested by program staff.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;5%:&lt;/b&gt;  SNAP-Ed Program Support: Provide basic office support for SNAP-Ed Program Assistant.Internal and external applicants are required to accurately self-disclose all criminal convictions when they apply. Final candidate offer is contingent upon the university's verification of credentials and other information required by law and/or university policies or practices based upon a criminal background check. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Seneca County</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52968</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:09-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:09-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52968"/>
    <title>Fiscal Associate</title>
    <content>Fiscal Associate provides support for the fiscal and procurement functions of the Department of English; maintains fiscal transaction records and files; initiates procurement and fiscal transactions; manages P-Cards for department; provides fiscal transaction information and reports to the department Fiscal/HR Manager; prepares and distributes monthly program and research activity reports; processes travel requests and reimbursements; makes travel arrangements; responds to inquiries and provides information on OSU and department fiscal policies and procedures; assists in preparing budgets; assists with reconciliation; makes deposits; organizes annual surplus order of furniture and out of service equipment; serves as the department Equipment Coordinator, which includes tracking capitalized and non-capitalized assets and completing annual equipment inventory audits; coordinates office space renovations; serves as back-up initiator for Payroll and Human Resources transactions.</content>
    <author>
      <name>English</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52977</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:14-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:14-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52977"/>
    <title>Senior Research Assoc-Social</title>
    <content>The Senior Research Associate position is an expert in early childhood development and education and serves as a content developer for the DoD Child Development Virtual Laboratory School. Content development includes authoring original training content based on peer reviewed research that supports best practices and the established curriculum of the Department of Defense. In addition, the Senior Research Associate manages and oversees project consultants who also contribute to content. Including reviewing and recommending revisions of written material for content and ensuring the written materials meet the needs of the Department of Defense. The Senior Research Associate will also supervise graduate research associates and work with post-doctoral staff who contribute content or assist with research activities. The Senior Research Associate is responsible for creating the training and curriculum design of the DoD Child Development Virtual Laboratory School. This position will be required to analyze and negotiate with the Department of Defense based on their home-based care provider training and development needs and the product being delivered by the project staff. Prepares and conducts presentations designed to educate members of the Department of Defense, staff members of each military service branch, project stakeholders and various professionals on the DoD Child Development Virtual Laboratory School. Manages and assists in the preparation of journal articles, proposals, reports, and educational materials for publication. This position will be required to establish and maintain working relationships with project sponsors and stakeholders. In addition, the Senior Research Associate will manage the submission of detailed research proposals to governmental and private agencies in collaboration with the Principle Investigator. The Senior Research Associate will select, design, and manage research methodology appropriate for current and proposed research activities. Teach classes as department needs and project needs allow.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Human Sciences Administration</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52961</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52961"/>
    <title>Open Faculty Search</title>
    <content>Teaches and advises undergraduate, graduate, and PhD level students in International Business; researchs in area of concentration; serves on department, college, and university committees.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Mgmt &amp; Human Resources</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53072</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:38-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:38-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53072"/>
    <title>Coor-Student Financial Aid Reg</title>
    <content>Provides counseling services and support in the Marion Campus Financial Aid Office and for our Delaware partnership location; counsels enrolled and prospective students, families, and other users; coordinates financial aid training for students and staff employees; researches and resolves problems; provides service on and off campus; makes presentations; participates in meetings and committees; collaborates with Advancement team regarding donor stewardship; completes special duties as assigned. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Marion Campus</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52848</id>
    <published>2014-02-15T01:03:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-15T01:03:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52848"/>
    <title>Finance Manager</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Summary:&lt;/b&gt;  
Assists with the annual budget process for OSU Advancement; works with directors to develop annual departmental budgets; performs budget analyses and utilizes information in GL, E-reports and other financial systems to generate and develop regular customized and ad hoc reports for departments and senior leadership; researches and resolves issues; analyzes expenditures, vacant positions, and cash carry forward account balances and makes recommendations on reallocations based on availability of funds; provides training and serves as point of contact for budget-related questions and concerns with Directors and staff; supervises staff; assists with General Ledger reconciliation to ensure accuracy, completeness, and proper reporting; assists with compliance review and fiscal duties; develops, analyzes and/or conducts quantitative and qualitative analysis of a broad range of Advancement data and/or processes as a basis for information dissemination, strategic planning, and decision making; analyzes data for validity, accuracy, and relevance; maintains various fundraising reports; serves as backup for chartfield creation and PeopleSoft access; represents Advancement to other University offices, administrators and outside agencies.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Duties&lt;/b&gt; 
Performs budget analyses and utilizes information in GL, E-reports and other financial systems to generate and develop regular customized and ad hoc reports for departments and senior leadership;   makes recommendations on reallocations based on availability of funds; maintains, balances, and reconciles departmental accounts on a regular basis; researches issues and/or concerns and resolves problems; analyzes expenditures, vacant positions, and cash carry forward account balances; documents procedures; works with directors to develop annual departmental budgets; provides training and serves as point of contact for budget-related questions and concerns with Directors and staff.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

Supervisory: Fosters an efficient and effective working environment by monitoring and coordinating the work of staff, developing work procedures, and ensuring that the resources needed to accomplish work are provided; making quality decisions and communicating these decisions/changes in a timely and appropriate manner; providing performance planning and feedback; consistently adhering to established policies and procedures; responding constructively to conflict and the demands of work; hiring and making salary-related recommendations; ensures accuracy of personal and team’s work.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

Conducts quantitative analyses of a broad range of data and performance metrics as a basis for strategic planning and decision making; completes departmental surveys; prepares monthly internal scorecard to measure progress of the campaign budget to campaign totals; maintains Campaign Dashboard fundraising reports university’s steering committee.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

Provides direct support of Alumni Association, ensures 501(c)3 compliance and accurate reporting, policy and procedure development and improvement and audit oversight; performs oversight of vendor performance of tax filing and certain aspects of Advancement Finance.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

Serves as back-up to fiscal office; assists with compliance review for purchases against University and department policies, guidelines and procedures, including purchase orders, travel requests reimbursements, and PCard expenditures; assists with chartfield maintenance and PS access; assists with General Ledger Reconciliation; serves on committees; other duties as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Development/OSU Foundation</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53056</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:14-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:14-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53056"/>
    <title>Director-00</title>
    <content>The Director of Operations will be responsible for the direct oversight and management of the day-to-day internal operations of the Student Financial Aid office. This individual must be a relationship builder as the primary components of the job are providing leadership and direction to managers and staff within the office and serving as a liaison with other departments, colleges and extended campuses. This position regularly interacts with all areas of Enrollment Services, colleges and academic support units at Ohio State, regulatory and governmental agencies, software vendors, both internal and external auditors, and university compliance officers.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

The Director of Operations manages the internal operations of the Student Financial Aid office in compliance with all federal, state, and NCAA regulations, as well as institutional policies, in order to authorize and coordinate $1 billion in total financial assistance, including loans, scholarships, grants and Federal Work Study, to 49,000 students in a manner consistent with the university’s mission. This individual will work closely with the Executive Director of Student Financial Aid to plan and implement the future direction of the office. The Director of Operations will also act as the primary liaison and work with the Director of the Student Service Center (SSC) to ensure that the SSC staff is providing quality financial aid information and customer service to students and parents.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;  

&lt;b&gt;Position Environment&lt;/b&gt;
The Director of Operations will report directly to the Executive Director while providing direct and indirect supervision to 52 staff members. This individual will work with colleges, the University Bursar, and other OSU departments, in addition to collaborating with financial aid communities in the Ohio/Midwest area.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Performance Objectives&lt;/b&gt;
Specifically, this position will be responsible for:
1. Providing leadership, oversight and direction to the office on a daily basis.
2. Managing internal operations of the Student Financial Aid office, directly supervising four Associate Directors and indirectly supervising Assistant Directors of all functional areas, including performance planning and management.
3. Providing oversight to systems analysis personnel in the development of computer applications and the SIS system, compliance and training personnel in the development of staff training programs, and scholarships and funds management personnel in the administration of all university merit and donor scholarship funds and the reconciliation of all federal and state financial aid programs.
4. Collaborating with the Executive Director in planning and implementing the current and future direction of the office.
5. Staying current with statewide, regional and national trends that may affect Ohio State and the university’s constituencies.
6. Directly overseeing salary/budget administration and assisting the Executive Director in establishing budget priorities.
7. Acting as a liaison with colleges and university departments, secondary school local communities and the general public, and representing the office with key university communities and task forces.
8. Communicating effectively with a diverse audience.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Student Financial Aid</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>51358</id>
    <published>2013-10-30T09:33:34-04:00</published>
    <updated>2013-10-30T09:33:34-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/51358"/>
    <title>Research Aide</title>
    <content>Assists the Manager of Stone Laboratory; assists in preparation of the summer program; assists in the operation of the Stone Lab Fieldtrip Program; assists in the operation of the Aquatic Visitor Center; assists in the preparation and maintenance of facilities for utilization by visitors, faculty, researchers, and students; provides assistance to secretary and laboratory managers as needed; conducts inventory of supplies and equipment; maintains and repairs scientific equipment; leads tours, science cruises, laboratory sessions, and activities for visiting groups; provides information about fieldtrip program; assists in construction and storage of educational displays; conducts orientation sessions for visiting groups; assists in seasonal set-up and close-down procedures for the laboratory and performs special assignments as needed. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Center/Lake Erie Area Research</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52995</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:30-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:30-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52995"/>
    <title>Cook 1</title>
    <content>This position serves as a cook for the Golf Course Restaurant serving both OSU Golf Club members and the general public; operates standard kitchen equipment to cook food; prepares and cooks main course dishes, side dishes, salads, desserts, dressings, beverages, and special menu items; assists with all general food prep including cleaning and cutting, and assembling trays; may assist in setting up food lines and serving food; cleans work area, utensils and equipment.  </content>
    <author>
      <name>Athletics</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53065</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:27-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:27-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53065"/>
    <title>Dining Utility Worker</title>
    <content>The Utility Worker maintains a clean, sanitary, and safe environment in a food service operation serving students, staff, and guests of the university; operates and sets up dishwashing equipment: cleans dish return systems and area; disposes of all trash and food waste; stocks and/or supplies dispenser equipment and food items; cleans and sets up beverage, soft serve and other service equipment; cleans kitchen equipment; ensures the refrigerators are clean and in accordance with prescribed standards; cleans and maintains kitchen and serving equipment; washes windows and light fixtures; maintains floor cleanliness by sweeping and mopping.  </content>
    <author>
      <name>Campus Grinds</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52755</id>
    <published>2014-02-08T01:03:41-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-08T01:03:41-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52755"/>
    <title>Post Doctoral Researcher</title>
    <content>Analyzes the presence and concentration of flavor compounds in the headspace of canned foods; determines if a correlation exists between these compounds and metallic corrosion in the cans; utilizes Selected Ion Flow Tube Mass Spectrometer and/or other appropriate laboratory analytical instruments (such as LC/MS, GC/MS, etc.) for analyses; researches how flavor compounds induce corrosion in cans; performs other types of laboratory duties closely related to food flavors, food chemistry, food processing, food packaging, and shelf life analysis; travels to food-related companies and give presentations as needed. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Food Science &amp; Technology</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52986</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:24-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:24-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52986"/>
    <title>Office Associate</title>
    <content>Works as part of the OSU Extension team in Ottawa County. The Office Associate provides general office support for all program area Extension Educators and good customer service to on-site visitors; assists with administrative/county operations for the county Extension Director and Extension Educators; and processes and maintains supply orders for program staff.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Position Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;b&gt;50%:&lt;/b&gt;  General Office Support and Customer Service: Answer telephones and serve as the primary first contact for on-site visitors; provide timely and relevant information to clientele without assistance when possible through distribution of fact sheets and other resources; open, sort and distribute daily mail, fax, and other communications; prepare newsletters and other large mailings, maintain bulk mail records; operate office equipment and troubleshoot when necessary; maintain a high level of professionalism at all times and protect confidential information; create and maintain records for program registration as requested by all program area Extension Educators; maintain the 4-H membership database as requested by the 4-H Educator; and provide basic office support for all program area Educators.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;35%:&lt;/b&gt;  Administrative/County Operations: Initiate payment of all invoices through appropriate procedures; monitor and track appropriated and non-appropriated university funds, reconcile e-Reports on a monthly basis, and provide monthly reports to the County Extension Director and other Educators, prepare and make deposits, and monitor and track local account funds, reconciling on a monthly basis and providing reports to the County Extension Director and other Educators.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;10%:&lt;/b&gt;  Orders and Inventories: Maintain an office supply inventory and order items as needed; and order program related supplies as requested by program staff.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;5%:&lt;/b&gt;  SNAP-Ed Program Support: Provide basic office support for SNAP-Ed Program Assistant.Internal and external applicants are required to accurately self-disclose all criminal convictions when they apply.  Final candidate offer is contingent upon the university's verification of credentials and other information required by law and/or university policies or practices based upon a criminal background check.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Ottawa County</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52970</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:10-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:10-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52970"/>
    <title>Staff Assistant-Grad School</title>
    <content>The Graduate School provides leadership for graduate education at The Ohio State University. It fosters quality in graduate education and research by ensuring high standards for 200 plus graduate degree programs and by providing essential services that support the work of approximately 10,000 graduate students and more than 3,000 graduate faculty and staff. Each of the regular 22 Graduate School staff members contributes both individually and collectively to meeting the mission of the Graduate School.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; 

This position assists the Director of Registration Services with the day to day administrative and supervisory responsibilities in the Registration Services area of the Graduate School; performs initial reviews of graduate conditional admission petitions for the Associate Dean; manages the English as a Second Language (ESL) compliance process including monitoring the completion of the composition requirement; prepares correspondence, e-mails, and reports relevant to various Registration Service’s job functions; maintains ESL and conditional admissions databases; assists with customer service, including greeting office visitors, answering phones, responding to e-mail inquiries, and researching and resolving problems; assists with preparation of work schedules for Registration Service's regular staff, student employees, and graduate associates and the distribution of work assignments; assists the Director of Graduation Services with the monitoring of enrollment and degree requirements for students enrolled in combined and/or dual degree graduate programs; assists with the certification process for interdisciplinary specializations, minors, and graduate specializations; serves as a liaison to departments and graduate programs; represents the Directors of Registration and Graduation Services at meetings; assists with special projects and programs as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Graduate School Administration</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52954</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:03:58-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:03:58-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52954"/>
    <title>Professor</title>
    <content>Serves as the Chase Chair; teaches undergraduate, graduate  and Ph.D. level courses in Management &amp; Human Resources; conducts research; serves on departmental and college committees.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Mgmt &amp; Human Resources</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52979</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:15-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:15-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52979"/>
    <title>Program Manager</title>
    <content>Trains others to implement Literacy Collaborative; provides leadership in designing and producing Literacy Collaborative training materials; creates/leads various literacy professional development events related to Literacy Collaborative; requires extensive travel; interprets evaluation data and standards for implementation; organizes and manages technical assistance for schools in the literacy network and uses primary level data to inform implementation of primary Literacy Collaborative training program; plans and leads meetings for university and school district level trainers; responsible for developing and managing a network that includes universities and districts; other duties as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Teaching &amp; Learning Admin</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52963</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52963"/>
    <title>Research Assistant 1-B/H</title>
    <content>Provides technical and intellectual assistance to a M.Sc. thesis research project examining physical and biological characteristics driving largemouth bass recruitment variability in Ohio reservoirs; participates in research of the Aquatic Ecology Lab; conducts field sampling of plankton, aquatic invertebrate, and fish using a variety of techniques; analyzes samples and data; performs age determination of otoliths; processes fish tissue for isotopic analysis; performs microscopy and image analysis; trains and supervises assistant technicians in sample processing; maintains equipment and the lab; analyzes data using various software programs; contributes to the development of the project and the lab; assists with administrative duties associated with a research project including purchasing research supplies, photocopying, drive motor vehicles, and preparing correspondence as needed.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Evol, Ecology &amp; Org Biology</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53074</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:38-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:38-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53074"/>
    <title>Program Coordinator</title>
    <content>The Ohio State University Libraries is currently seeking applications for a Non-Roman Languages Coordinator within the Collections and Technical Services Division to coordinate, plan, develop, evaluate, and supervise Non-Roman Languages cataloging within the University Libraries. Successful candidates will possess experience planning and overseeing cataloging in several foreign languages, experience supervising, delegating and motivating a team, and strong organizational, analytical, and problem solving skills. Under the supervision of the Head of Cataloging the position will lead the Non-Latin Languages Section and will be responsible for:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; 

Managing and supervising 6.5 staff in the Non-Roman Language Section, including hiring and training of staff and students assistants; working closely with the OSU Language and Area Studies department defining workflows and  solving cataloging issues; develops and maintains collegial relationships with key library departments particularly Acquisitions, Information Technology, and Preservation and Reformatting departments; performing original and complex copy cataloging of materials representing all levels of difficulty, all subjects and all formats according to RDA, LCRIs, LCSH, LC classification and MARC formats; participating in the NACO, SACO, and BIBCO components of the Program for Cooperative Cataloging (PCC) and performing authority work in accordance with local and national standards and guidelines; solving problems related to obsolete or incorrect information appearing in bibliographic and holdings records and well as assisting staff and student assistants in solving problems and achieving high level of accuracy; keeping current with revisions to cataloging rules and trends, bringing revisions to the attention of the Head of Cataloging and assisting in the implementation of changes in the department, including the potential services and technologies; preparing monthly report of the Non-Roman Section activities; maintaining the Non-Roman Languages website and blog.</content>
    <author>
      <name>University Libraries</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52852</id>
    <published>2014-02-15T01:03:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-15T01:03:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52852"/>
    <title>Technology Licensing Officer</title>
    <content>Supports the management of the University's confidential patent portfolio; tracks patent prosecution matters on a case by case basis; researches, compiles, organizes and presents information to licensing officers relevant to the patent portfolio; reports patent prosecution matters and billings to appropriate individuals within the department; develops Standard Operating Procedures for coordinating patent prosecution and legal review of the portfolio; establishes and maintains electronic files for patent applications and issued patents and technologies; interacts with legal representatives regarding TCO patent prosecution, procedures and billing matters; reviews invoices for consistency and accuracy in conjunction with licensing officer; creates summary detail reports to track invoices and follow individual fiscal activity by law firm or attorney.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Technology Licensing</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53058</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:15-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:15-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53058"/>
    <title>Program Coordinator</title>
    <content>Provides support for the development team focusing on hematologic cancers and special events at The Ohio State James Cancer Hospital and Solve Research Institute.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Development/OSU Foundation</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52997</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:30-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:30-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52997"/>
    <title>Dining Utility Worker</title>
    <content>The Utility Worker maintains a clean, sanitary, and safe environment in a food service operation serving students, staff, and guests of the university; operates and sets up dishwashing equipment and cleans dish return systems and area; disposes of all trash and food waste; stocks and/or supplies dispenser equipment and food items; cleans and sets up beverage, soft serve and other service equipment; cleans kitchen equipment; ensures the refrigerators are clean and in accordance with prescribed standards; cleans and maintains kitchen and serving equipment; washes windows and light fixtures; maintains floor cleanliness by sweeping and mopping.  </content>
    <author>
      <name>Morrill Commons</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52956</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:03:59-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:03:59-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52956"/>
    <title>Assistant Professor</title>
    <content>Teaches undergraduate and graduate courses in finance; conducts research; publishes; serves on departmental, college, and university committees.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Finance</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53067</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:29-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53067"/>
    <title>Lecturer</title>
    <content>The Ohio State University at Mansfield is accepting applications for a full-time Lecturer in Spanish. The appointment will be effective  Autumn Semester, 2014, and will involve teaching various courses constituting the university's three-semester sequence of General Education courses intended to develop oral and written competencies in Spanish.  Additional courses taught in English which involve Hispanic cultural study or comparative literature may be part of the person's teaching load, depending upon background and interest. The possibility exists for additional teaching during summers. This appointment, while not tenure eligible, is renewable. The M.A. in Spanish is required, although the Ph.D. is preferred. Successful Spanish teaching at the college level is also preferred. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Mansfield Campus</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52989</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52989"/>
    <title>Custodial Worker</title>
    <content>The Custodial Worker maintains a safe and clean environment in and around assigned Student Life residence halls, offices and other properties for student residents, guests and staff; responsible for day-to-day cleaning as well as other housekeeping duties involved with special housing operations; cleans rooms, offices and public areas; cleans most flat surfaces, furniture, windows, vents, and light fixtures; may count, issue, and receive linen; operates basic electrical cleaning equipment; maintains floors and carpets, moves furniture, removes trash, clears snow, and cleans building entrances and walkways; reports any damage or theft discovered in work area; may be asked to respond to emergencies; climbs ladders and scaffolding.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Housekeeping-South District</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52972</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52972"/>
    <title>Business Manager 2</title>
    <content>Serves as administrative office manager for the office of the Vice President and Enterprise Executive for Energy and Environment; reports directly to the Associate Director; assists all senior office staff and other university leaders to coordinate the numerous programs and projects of the office; provides support in all aspects of daily administrative and operational functions; responds to inquiries and requests; works under minimal supervision; develops and initiates administrative procedures; makes decisions according to established policies and procedures; determines and is responsible for ensuring that appropriate action is taken to meet goals and guidelines; provides fiscal and personnel services for the office including creation of reports and analysis; prepares and monitors budgets including various facility renovation and construction projects; works with Office of Research (OR) and Office of Academic Affairs (OAA) Service Centers to establish oversight of procurement, financial, personnel, payroll, and operational processing environment to ensure adherence to established office and university controls structures; prepares, oversees and maintains reports and documentations; creates and coordinates the preparation of financial statements; prepares budget projections and plans; provides routine and complex administrative support; researches and analyzes materials, information, programs, procedures and policies, provides technical and strategic advice to aid senior staff in decision-making; represents the office to other administrators and outside agencies; participates in the preparation of contract budgets, grant applications, and proposals; takes on special projects as assigned by the Interim Director; serves as department Asset Manager.  </content>
    <author>
      <name>Office of Energy &amp; Environment</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52999</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:31-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:31-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52999"/>
    <title>Research Interviewer</title>
    <content>Coordinates and performs collection of data from respondents using various equipment; conducts personal and telephone interviews with respondents.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Ctr/Human Resource Rsch</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52981</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:20-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:20-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52981"/>
    <title>Research Assistant 2-B/H</title>
    <content>Performs field and laboratory studies focused on water quality analysis for ongoing watershed research; conducts nutrient, solids and flow analysis utilizing auto analyzer, sonde and continuous flow monitoring technology; collects bi-monthly in stream water samples and continuous flow monitoring data; performs statistical analysis of data; tabulates data and conducts library research of literature and prepares draft reports; performs routine maintenance on lab and field equipment; responsible for maintaining current laboratory inventory, hygiene and safety plans.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Sch of Environ &amp; Natural Res</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52965</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52965"/>
    <title>Registered Veterinary Tech</title>
    <content>Participates as an active team member in the Small Animal Surgery section of the Veterinary Medical Center and surgical patient receiving; organizes, directs, and provides helpful and collegial assistance to professional students, clinicians, residents, and technical students during receiving appointment hours; coordinates with Reception; assists with patient exams; prepares and labels specimens; assists with receiving surgical emergencies, on call duties, client communication with phone calls and release instructions; prepares animals and equipment for surgery: clips, shaves and scrubs body area(s) to be operated; sets up appropriate equipment and instruments for each case; prepares and labels specimens obtained in surgery; assists surgeons during surgical procedures using aseptic techniques; cleans and disinfects operating rooms, equipment and related areas; demonstrates and observes veterinary students in operating room procedures; other duties as assigned; possible exposure to rabies and other zoonotic diseases, animal inflicted injuries: bites, scratches, etc. and anesthetic gases, formalin, bleach.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Veterinary Hospital</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53076</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:40-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:40-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53076"/>
    <title>Systems Developer/Engineer</title>
    <content>Provides IT support to the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE) and The Simulation Innovation and Modeling Center (SIMCenter); support includes systems administration, hardware maintenance, networking, printing, installing and debugging 3rd party software systems, maintaining and writing custom scripts, user consultation; works with College of Engineering and OSU IT communities in support of common projects and tools; creates, analyzes and plans complex IT solutions to address identifiable needs; researches IT industry advancements for future applications; responds to and remediates IT security events/threats; administers the department's and center's desktops, workstations, and servers; oversees network operations; completes end user requests and incidents through resolution; recommends and orders hardware/software while recognizing cost-effectiveness; manages and maintains equipment inventory of all capitalized and non-capitalized items; ensures compliance with university and college policies, initiatives, and mandates.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Electrical &amp; Computer Engr.</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52861</id>
    <published>2014-02-15T01:03:41-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-15T01:03:41-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52861"/>
    <title>Air Quality Technician 1</title>
    <content>The Air Quality Technician 1 provides general, preventive, and mechanical maintenance to assigned Student Life buildings and operations, which may include Campus Dining Operations; performs skilled installation and repair of air conditioning, refrigeration and heating, building mechanical and electrical equipment, domestic water and drainage systems; works on pneumatic and electric/electronic controls; repairs and replaces air compressors, pumps, belts, bearings, fans, motors and filters; repairs steam traps and installs piping; repairs commercial kitchen equipment; inspects and maintains life safety systems; inspects and performs preventive maintenance; may serve as a functional crew leader; must be able to climb ladders and scaffolding and operate personnel lifts; subject to 24-hour emergency call-in; may work overtime. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Oval Community Maintenance</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53060</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:19-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:19-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53060"/>
    <title>Program Coordinator</title>
    <content>Provides support for the major gift function of the Athletics Development Office; responsible for the planning, organizing and execution of all special events from induction to completion; assists by documenting policies, procedures, best practices, and templates for event planning and execution; responds to ad hoc requests from University Development Donor Relations as appropriate; provides excellent customer service to inquiries from staff, donors, university administrators and other constituents, maintaining a high level of confidentiality; manages or executes other projects as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Development/OSU Foundation</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52379</id>
    <published>2014-01-18T01:04:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-01-18T01:04:29-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52379"/>
    <title>Open Faculty Search</title>
    <content>As The Ohio State University charts a course from excellence to eminence, the University Libraries is seeking a leader with strong skills in analysis, innovation, and collaboration to care for collections that underpin this evolution. The Head of Preservation and Reformatting plays a leading role in the life-cycle management of the Libraries' collections, directing and advancing a diverse portfolio of related services encompassing conservation, preservation, and reformatting of collections. The position reports to the Associate Director for Collections, Technical Services, and Scholarly Communication and manages units that include 14 staff and 6 student assistants. The Head of Preservation and Reformatting will work in a highly integrated environment to create and implement innovative approaches to providing efficient stewardship of its collections. Programs within the department include digitization, bindery and end-processing, conservation and treatment, and electronic reserves. The Head is also the Chief Preservation Officer for the University Libraries. The Ohio State University Libraries hold over seven million volumes plus a diversity of special and archival collections in a wide range of formats and multiple library facilities including a high-density storage unit. Digital reformatting is an area of current growth and development in concert with a range of investments in fostering the discovery and use of distinctive collections held by the University Libraries. Partnerships with other libraries are integral to preservation and digitization strategies for University Libraries. The Head will operate in an environment of active consortial engagement through the CIC, HathiTrust, OhioLINK,and other cooperative programs. The Libraries are also currently lending collections for scanning to the Google Books Project with the CIC. Key Responsibilities include: Provides vision, focus, and leadership for reformatting, conservation and preservation activities within the Libraries; Functions as the Libraries' chief preservation officer, serving as a preservation advocate and leading in planning for activities such as disaster response, supporting space planning to ensure appropriate environmental conditions for housing collections in all formats, etc.; Manages the department's programs including digitization, conservation, end processing, bindery prep, e-reserves and the Libraries' Logan Elm Press; Develops and implements strategy for in-house and outsourced reformatting of the Libraries distinctive collections; Maintains a robust conservation program with support for the Libraries' active exhibitions program; Develops policies and specifications related to preservation and reformatting Library collections; Manages preservation budgets and endowments and contributes to grant development related to preservation and digitization; Contributes to planning and leadership within the Collections, Technical Services and Scholarly-Communication Division; Contributes to planning and developing digital preservation strategy for the Libraries; Builds and maintains a research program and service profile related to preservation and/or digital reformatting; Presents and publishes in appropriate venues in order to raise the profile of both yourself and the Libraries. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Collection &amp; Technical Srvcs</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52958</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:00-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52958"/>
    <title>Assistant Professor</title>
    <content>Teaches undergraduate and graduate courses in finance; conducts research; publishes; serves on departmental, college, and university committees.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Finance</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53069</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:33-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:33-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53069"/>
    <title>Employee &amp; Labor Relations Consultant</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;The Opportunity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ohio State University, one of the nation’s leading public universities, is seeking a flexible and resilient Employee &amp; Labor Relations Consultant to serve in the Office of Human Resources’ Employee and Labor Relations department. The position requires a consultative and collaborative individual capable of building solid relationships throughout the university and at all levels of the organization.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
With a service-oriented approach, the individual will provide human resource consultation and services with specific emphasis on employee and labor relations as a member of a consulting team. These duties include providing information, training and consultation to college and departmental administrators, managers, human resource professionals, faculty and staff regarding a variety of ER/LR issues from performance management to the interpretation and implementation of federal/state regulations and OSU HR policies. Similarly, the successful Employee &amp; Labor Relations Consultant will come to know their customer groups so well that they will be able to proactively identify potential areas of risk and develop and implement action plans for resolution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Ultimately, the day to day duties of the position calls for an individual who is prepared to conduct complex investigations and who recognizes the personal and organizational value of this process for the institution. While investigations can be challenging at times, they are vital to the achievement of the university values. The successful individual in this role will display a high level of comfort and resilience with fluctuating and shifting situations and, at times, will experience a heavy workload. The role will also be a rewarding one as the successful candidate will form strong relationships with his/her customer base resulting in the creation of a sustained trusted advisory role. In addition, the Employee &amp; Labor Relations Consultant will partner with their teammates and the larger OSU community to achieve the unit and university strategic goals. The successful candidate will be a self-starting team player, able to maintain objectivity while performing their duties and who values integrity, diversity and the importance of having fun along the way. In the first 90 days, the successful candidate will understand their role in the organization and how the work they perform supports the larger mission of the university.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Performance Objectives&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Specifically, this position will be responsible for:
1. Investigating discrimination and sexual harassment complaints, workplace violence allegations, and other cases of a complex nature; and issuing written reports to the unit and the employee with specific action steps, as appropriate. 
2. Providing confidential, proactive and objective consultation to various constituencies.
3. Collaborating to develop and implement effective practices that result in a healthy culture.
4. Reviewing departments’ adherence to guidelines, procedures and employment laws and regulations.
5. Identifying and analyzing specific employee and management actions regarding employee relations policies, procedures and documentation.
6. Integrating work/life and diversity principles into consultation practices and providing training regarding these and other employee relations issues.
7. Interpreting bargaining unit agreements while establishing and maintaining satisfactory labor-management relationships.
8. Assisting with problem/conflict resolution before escalation to formal grievance or corrective action.
9. Serving as Hearing Officer for corrective action and/or grievance meetings and developing and issuing appropriate written responses.
10. Leading meetings involving the Crisis Assessment Team.
11. Analyzing trends to find actionable, pragmatic solutions to employee relations issues.
12. Assisting in the development and/or revision of employee relations programs, policies and tools that align with university objectives of promoting a high performance culture with an emphasis on creativity, flexibility, coaching, feedback and accountability.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Organization &amp; HR Consulting</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53053</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:01-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:01-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53053"/>
    <title>Associate Director</title>
    <content>Serves as the lead academic advisor managing and working closely with the three members of the advising team responsible for the FTMBA, WPMBA, and Specialized Masters; coordinates efforts to ensure best practices and innovation; serves as the primary academic advisor for the students in the Graduate Minor in Health Sciences; builds partnerships with colleges where there might be opportunities to create dual degrees; serves as the liaison between Fisher's recruiting and admissions team and student services; responsible for the donor stewardship for all of the graduate degree programs.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB GPO - Admin</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52991</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52991"/>
    <title>Housekeeping Manager 2</title>
    <content>The Housekeeping Manager 2 provides leadership and direction for environmental services to assigned buildings or areas as workload requirements vary, such as summer semester and break periods; HM may be assigned to supervise in different work areas; leads and coaches subordinate managers, supervisors and custodial team; assists with the training and development of custodial staff; responsible for overall performance management of staff; makes hiring and corrective action decisions in coordination with supervisor; participates on management team and develops relationships with colleagues; manages and shares resources; solves problems; communicates constructively with all contacts; promotes safety and security principles.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Housekeeping-West District</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52974</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52974"/>
    <title>Senior Graphic Designer</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Position Overview&lt;/b&gt;
The Ohio State University must communicate to the world in the most innovative, leading-edge, boundary-pushing ways. The Senior Graphic Designer serves as the creative lead on projects that have a strategic focus while spanning a wide variety of subject matter and target audiences. This role designs and develops creative solutions across a range of media to ensure impactful visual communications. This conceptual communicator reports to the Creative Director and works closely with the Art Director and creative team.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;   

&lt;b&gt;Organizational Overview&lt;/b&gt;
The Senior Graphic Designer is part of the Brand and Marketing team within University Communications. University Communications is part of a broader Office of Advancement that combines and coordinates communication, engagement and fundraising efforts. Advancement exists to support the university by increasing awareness of, engagement in and giving to Ohio State. These efforts are all in service to the greater university vision: The Ohio State University will be the world’s preeminent public comprehensive university, solving problems of world-wide significance.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;  

Brand and Marketing is a fast-paced team, enveloped in changing paradigms in a sometimes ambiguous environment. Asking questions is encouraged and support is provided to ensure career growth.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; 

&lt;b&gt;Performance Objectives&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; 

1.	During the first 90 days:&lt;/b&gt;
a.	Become very well-versed on the brand guidelines and overall department functions and goals
b.	Quickly build rapport across departments
c.	Begin contributing to creative project meetings
d.	Take the visual lead on 2-3 projects&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; 

&lt;b&gt;2.	During the first 3-6 months&lt;/b&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;
a.	Consistently apply brand guidelines 
b.	Consistently produce outstanding design
c.	Deeply engage with the creative, brand and project management teams
d.	Become savvy on navigating University Communications</content>
    <author>
      <name>Marketing Communications</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53001</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:32-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:32-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53001"/>
    <title>Research Assistant 1-B/H</title>
    <content>Provides assistance with field and laboratory research on woodland salamanders; collects data on woodland salamanders within the forest strand of southeast Ohio; collects woody and herbaceous vegetation data from field and lab experiments; identifies amphibians and plants of the region; performs analyses on forestry and wildlife vegetation to determine composition of forests within control sites; establishes and maintains plots within forest strands; keeps logs and enters data collected in laboratory and field experiments using spreadsheets; performs quality assurance checks on data and equipment.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Sch of Environ &amp; Natural Res</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52983</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:23-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:23-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52983"/>
    <title>Fiscal Officer</title>
    <content>Serves as the fiscal administrative advisor to the Chair of The Department of Teaching and Learning (T&amp;L), providing data to help with long-term and big-picture planning; provides budget management and oversight for complex unit and related Department programs including ESL/ALP (English Second Language and Language Program), and RREL (Reading Recovery and Early Literacy); provides a broad range of fiscal services for the department including creation of financial reports and analysis, PBA &amp; cash budgeting, and expense control &amp; revenue enhancements; prepares and monitors budgets for general funds, conferences, earnings, grants and contracts, OSP grants, development, agency and plant funds in compliance with University policies and College guidelines; provides revenue and expense analysis on student credit hour generation and research activity; provides recommendations and advice for administrative financial decisions; responsible for oversight and management of the fiscal Service Center functions and supervises support staff; responsible for oversight and maintenance of the established procurement, financial and operational processing environment to ensure adherence to established internal controls structures and University, College, and unit policies/procedures including, but not limited to, appropriate segregation of duties in the processing of all financial transactions, payroll controls, appropriate mandatory approvals and reconciliations; position has a dotted reporting line relationship to the College Senior Fiscal Officer; initiates budget and fund transfers; establishes department fiscal policy and process as necessary; represents department to outside administrators; serves on College and University committees; other duties as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Teaching &amp; Learning Admin</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52967</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:08-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:08-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52967"/>
    <title>Program Coord-Special Events</title>
    <content>Communications and Events Coordinator for the Center for Languages, Literatures, and Cultures (CLLC); manages social media including blogs, brochures, press releases, and digital signage; develops high-quality, professional communications to promote programs, activities and events for the CLLC and for the departments in Hagerty Hall; serves as the event planner for the CLLC and the departments in Hagerty Hall; plans, coordinates, and manages all logistical and facility arrangements for campus and off-campus events; provides content and graphic materials from concept to dissemination.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Ctr-Language, Lit &amp; Culture</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53079</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T14:58:15-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T14:58:15-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53079"/>
    <title>Disability Case Manager</title>
    <content>Are you looking for the next step in your career?  Do you want to be a part of team that helps improve the lives of the people that they serve?  The Ohio State University’s Integrated Disability department is a robust team that maintains a &lt;b&gt;proactive, fast-paced approach to case management&lt;/b&gt;. The department services the entire university and Wexner Medical Center, so our Disability Program Managers provide consultative services to an &lt;b&gt;unparalleled variety of employees&lt;/b&gt;. This diversity fosters a &lt;b&gt;continuous expansion of knowledge&lt;/b&gt; about a variety of professions and work environments.

The team is comprised of &lt;b&gt;critical, forward-thinking team-players&lt;/b&gt;, who are challenged every day with new opportunities to improve the lives of Ohio State University employees.   Since its inception, our innovative Transitional Work program has maintained an extremely high return-to-work rate, which has resulted in savings to the university in excess of 13 million dollars.  The following information further details the Disability Program Manager role and the opportunity to impact the university, but the message is simple - the Integrated Disability team's &lt;b&gt;commitment to excellence&lt;/b&gt; in service permeates every aspect of what we do, and we are looking for the next team-member to &lt;b&gt;join our mission&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Opportunity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Integrated Disability lies within the Office of Human Resources at The Ohio State University.  The department assists faculty and staff in linking with appropriate disability benefits, including Short and Long Term Disability, workers' compensation, and state retirement systems.  Additionally, Integrated Disability assists with the evaluation and provision of reasonable accommodations, oversees the disability separation process, coordinates medical leaves, remain-at-work and return-to-work services, unemployment benefits, and other programs for employees that become disabled. 

Under the direction of the Team Lead for Transitional Work, the Disability Program Manager provides proactive, individualized case management services for employees with occupational and/or non-occupational illnesses and injuries. The position is charged with determining an employee’s temporary or long-term accommodation needs to assist them in achieving employment goals.  The Disability Program Manager coordinates efforts with various entities, including medical providers, managed care organizations (MCO), disability carriers, OSU ancillary services, third party administrators (TPA), and state agencies to assure continuity of services. Along with overseeing daily claim activities, the Disability Program Manager drafts and implements return-to-work plans and recommendations for employees and their employing departments, and provides vocational rehabilitation services for workers’ compensation claims. While maintaining consistent contact with the employee, the Disability Program Manager works collaboratively with managers, Human Resource Professionals, the Americans with Disabilities Act Coordinator, legal services and employee and labor relations to ensure successful execution of transitional work agreements and accommodation plans. 
The Disability Program Manager utilizes a sophisticated case management system to aid in case documentation and reporting.  The extensive documentation of cases and the development of valuable reports help to ensure compliance with university, state and federal policies. In addition to documenting individual claims data, the Disability Program Manager provides disability trending, return-to-work statistics and OSHA metrics to business partners across the university and medical center on a regular basis. This individual also provides formal trainings to their assigned departments related to Integrated Disability services including disability benefits and accommodations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Environment&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This position reports to the Team Lead for Transitional Work within Integrated Disability. The Integrated Disability department is under the direction of the Manager of Integrated Disability and Unemployment and the Associate Director of Compliance Risk Management, Policies and Procedures. A successful candidate will possess strong organizational skills and be able to address multiple projects at the same time.  A high volume of cases coupled with outside project work can be expected.   In addition to the external collaborations with vendors and university departments highlighted above, there is also a strong collaborative culture within the department of Integrated Disability.  In addition to the Disability Program Manager role, the Integrated Disability team is also comprised of Leave Administrators, Claims Managers, a Job Developer, and an onsite Physical Therapist.</content>
    <author>
      <name>OHR Integrated Disability</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53062</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:24-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:24-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53062"/>
    <title>Systems Specialist-A&amp;P</title>
    <content>Serves as technical support for University Advancement and responds to requests for technical assistance in person, via phone or electronically; responsible for proper incident and problem management processes; logs all service desk interactions and redirects problems to appropriate resources; participates in the creating of FAQs and the Knowledge Base; assists in the development and updating of system documentations and standards for desktops, laptops and printers and advises customers regarding system software and hardware enhancements; requires good communication skills with the ability to work independently.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Development/OSU Foundation</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52976</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:13-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:13-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52976"/>
    <title>Assistant Vice President</title>
    <content>As a member of University Communication’s leadership team, the Assistant Vice President for Strategic Issues Management provides oversight and direction for pan-university issues of reputational significance; creates integrated communications strategies for effective handling of large reputational issues; develops positive approaches to promoting institutional goals, objectives and messaging; oversees execution of strategy; measures and evaluates outcomes; this position reports to the VP of University Communications and maintains a strong partnership with the AVP, Media and Public Relations.</content>
    <author>
      <name>University Communications</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52960</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52960"/>
    <title>Open Faculty Search</title>
    <content>Teaches and advises undergraduate, graduate, and PhD level students in Management Sciences; researchs in area of concentration; serves on department, college, and university committees.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Management Sciences</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53071</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:37-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:37-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53071"/>
    <title>Security Officer</title>
    <content>Provides physical security for assigned university facilities. Performs customer service functions such as answering directional questions, providing escorts to nearby campus locations, and providing assistance to disabled patrons; patrols buildings and grounds, and monitors fire and security alarms; works in security control room monitoring CCTV cameras, answering telephone, dispatching security officers and maintaining radio contact; administers first aid; operates fire extinguishers; investigates and reports on fires, crimes, unusual incidents, complaints, injuries and accidents.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Security &amp; Protective Serv</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53055</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:14-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:14-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53055"/>
    <title>Program Coordinator</title>
    <content>This position contributes to the international dimension of The Ohio State University by providing program support to the Global Gateways of The Ohio State University; coordinates day-to-day operations and program activities for the Gateways; serves as a liaison and point of contact on programs and activities for Gateway offices overseas and Ohio State academic units; researches and tracks Ohio State collaborations in Gateway regions; builds and manages relationships with the Office of International Affairs and Academic and Support Units, including but not limited to Colleges, Professional Schools, Regional Campuses, Student Life, Legal Affairs and the Global Gateways; shares information with the central communications unit of the Office of International Affairs, which is responsible for publicizing and communicating the range of international activities in which Ohio State is involved; plans, schedules, and executes events to further the goals of the Global Gateway office; serves as the Ohio State program manager for the Universitas21 relationship.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Office of International Affair</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52993</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:29-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52993"/>
    <title>Accountant</title>
    <content>Serves as delegated buyer for PeopleSoft Procurement, also responsible for all functions associated with Accounts Payable, Accounts Receivables, fund/journal transfers, travel related procurement/reimbursement, and WOSU product sales; responsible for year-end Asset Management reviews/reconciliations and maintenance of capital and non-capital equipment listings as per OSU policy; responsible for monthly fiscal expense/revenue reconciliations as per policy; assists the Business Manager in all internal/external audit requests/requirements; serves as initial contact regarding fiscal policy matters; reviews expenditures and revenues for appropriateness and accuracy; resolves differences; prepares monthly and year-end closing journals; prepares and updates internal procurement website information for staff; represents department to outside agencies and University administrators upon request.</content>
    <author>
      <name>WOSU Stations</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53064</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:27-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:27-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53064"/>
    <title>Open Faculty Search</title>
    <content>The overall role of the Regional Director, Operations, is to provide leadership to the Extension operations within the Southwest region comprised of 19 counties, including all matters affecting personnel, finance, public relations and business operations. As Associate Chair, the Regional Director works closely with the Department Chair in carrying out responsibilities associated with promotion and tenure development/direction. The Regional Director, Operations, works collaboratively with the OSU Extension administrative cabinet and Extension employees, numerous advisory committee members, volunteer stakeholders, public officials and other community leaders and volunteers in the region. Internal and external applicants are required to accurately self-disclose all criminal convictions when they apply. Final candidate offer is contingent upon the university's verification of credentials and other information required by law and/or university policies or practices based upon a criminal background check. </content>
    <author>
      <name>SouthWest Region OSU Extension</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52985</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:24-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:24-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52985"/>
    <title>Office Associate</title>
    <content>Provides primary office support for assigned teams; serves as first line of public contact for sport offices and acts as an information point for those sport offices; welcomes all guests, student-athletes and recruits visiting sport offices; coordinates daily office functions; produces and coordinates correspondence, mass mailings, memos, forms and lists at the request of the coaches; opens, sorts, and distributes mail; answers phones, screens calls, responds to inquiries and provides visitors with information; maintains student-athlete and parent contact information; maintains recruiting databases and enters information into department's BUCKS system; prepares competition contracts for all home events; coordinates competition officials contracts and payments; assists with individual coaches and team travel coordination and associated procedures; orders supplies; performs other related duties as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Athletics</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52969</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:10-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:10-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52969"/>
    <title>Program Manager</title>
    <content>Trains others to implement Literacy Collaborative; provides leadership in designing and producing Literacy Collaborative training materials; creates/leads various literacy professional development events related to Literacy Collaborative; requires extensive travel; interprets evaluation data and standards for implementation; organizes and manages technical assistance for schools in the literacy network and uses primary level data to inform implementation of primary Literacy Collaborative training program; plans and leads meetings for university and school district level trainers; responsible for developing and managing a network that includes universities and districts; other duties as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Teaching &amp; Learning Admin</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52978</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:14-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:14-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52978"/>
    <title>IRB Protocol Analyst</title>
    <content>Manages regulated human research protocols on assigned board(s) with a minimum of direction; coordinates Institutional Review Board (IRB) member activities; understands and applies federal regulations, state laws, and human research protection program policies to ensure compliance with sponsor and university requirements; analyzes research submissions and provides guidance to principal investigators and research teams; documents regulatory findings, technical board deliberations and actions; communicates with investigators and assists researchers to secure timely board approvals; continually monitors timelines to avoid delays and approval lapses; identifies customer service needs; participates in business process improvements and the development of educational programs; may conduct training sessions for research teams and Board members; relative distribution of duties varies with review board assignment.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Responsible Research Practices</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52962</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:01-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52962"/>
    <title>Program Coordinator</title>
    <content>Plans, coordinates, and implements programs and activities for the Resource Center for Medieval and Slavic Studies (RCMSS); coordinates international scholar visits; coordinates conferences and events; provides information to students, faculty, researchers, and the public regarding the RCMSS; develops and distributes written communications for the RCMSS; writes newsletters, plans events and assists with communications for multiple language and culture departments located in Hagerty Hall.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Slavic &amp; East European L&amp;C</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53073</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:38-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:38-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53073"/>
    <title>Director-A5</title>
    <content>Serves as the Chief Information Officer for the College of Food, Agricultural and Environmental Sciences; duties to include defining strategy and providing leadership for central and distributed College IT staff, College IT infrastructure and architecture, including related interfaces with other university and external systems, application development, networks, outsourcing, academic, research, outreach and business unit support, reengineering business processes, and customizing solutions to support teaching, research, outreach and administration; tracks a broad range of emerging technologies to determine their maturity and applicability to the College and its educational, research and outreach missions; assesses the relative impact of emerging technology to strategic needs and interprets their meaning to senior organization leadership team; understands the College's collective IT competencies and their value to the units individually and to the College as a whole; determines long-term College IT needs and develops strategy for systems development, acquisition and integration; leads College technology planning and policy development, aligning a current knowledge and future vision of technology and systems with the College's goals; partners with College leadership and departments to provide overall leadership and strategic planning for the College's IT budget, ensuring the IT budget supports the College's strategic plan; closely partners with departmental Chairs and school Directors, College leadership, various committees and internal stakeholders on strategies, planning, procurement and other areas of common interest; serves as member of the leadership team for the College and influences strategic decisions regarding the use of technology; and represents the College's IT interests and ambitions to the university's OCIO, as well as intramural and extramural peer organizations.</content>
    <author>
      <name>OSUE Administration</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52850</id>
    <published>2014-02-15T01:03:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-15T01:03:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52850"/>
    <title>Project Manager</title>
    <content>&lt;b&gt;Summary&lt;/b&gt;
Works closely with the university’s Principal Gifts team and develops and writes persuasive, donor-centered content for the university’s highest-capacity alumni and friends in a fast-paced, collaborative environment. Serves as lead on developing new, creative and highly personal approaches for reaching and influencing members of this specialized audience. Self-directs projects and successfully balances creativity and discipline to meet high expectations under tight deadlines. Builds and maintains knowledge of the university’s fundraising objectives and strategies and top donors and serves as a valuable resource and partner with a variety of stakeholders. Creates and implements a highly organized approach to managing projects, client needs and production of content that effectively targets top donors and prospects.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;  

&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;
Works closely with the central Principal Gift’s team and unit-based development colleagues to create highly customized communications strategies and solutions to effectively cultivate, solicit and steward the university’s highest-capacity alumni and friends, including individuals and organizations. Manages projects aimed at this specialized audience that meet fundraising objectives and contribute to a consistently branded donor experience, coordinating with team members and other partners to ensure 100% accuracy and timely execution. Serves as lead on developing new, creative and highly personal approaches for reaching and influencing the university’s top donors and prospects; develops strategy for and writes persuasive, donor-centered content (written, graphic, video, etc.) that resonates with the university’s highest-capacity alumni and friends and inspires them to give further to Ohio State, including highly personalized proposals, reports, briefings, feature stories and more. Works with subject matter experts throughout the university to gather and confirm information. Aligns work with university, campaign and unit-, priority- and project-specific messaging. Implements university style, voice and tone, and brand standards across all work. Collaborates with designers when needed to ensure high-impact materials; other duties as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Development/OSU Foundation</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53057</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:15-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:15-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53057"/>
    <title>Program Manager</title>
    <content>Acts independently as the program manager for an assigned portfolio of advancement events. Demonstrates and applies a level of consistency and a standard of excellence to designing and implementing events for the purpose of expanding awareness of, advocacy for, engagement in and giving to Ohio State. Partners with colleagues in The Ohio State University Alumni Association, University Development, University Communications and colleges/units. </content>
    <author>
      <name>Development/OSU Foundation</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52996</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:30-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:30-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52996"/>
    <title>Research Associate 2-B/H</title>
    <content>Manages daily operations of laboratory and assists in training of personnel; designs and executes experiments for research projects; maintains experimental data and prepares scientific reports and manuscripts; maintains records of clinical and biological samples; conducts specific assay following General Lab Practice guidelines; prepares presentations and manages manuscript and grant writing; supervises and trains coworkers, post-docs, visiting scholars and faculty on high performance liquid chromatography, mass spectrometry and wet chemistry protocols; tracks budget for specific projects.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Food Science &amp; Technology</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52955</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:03:59-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:03:59-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52955"/>
    <title>Assistant Professor</title>
    <content>Teaching and research in the field of Marketing; researches, serves on committees, and advises students.</content>
    <author>
      <name>FCOB Marketing &amp; Logistics</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>53066</id>
    <published>2014-03-01T01:05:27-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-03-01T01:05:27-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/53066"/>
    <title>Asst Director of Development</title>
    <content>The Associate Director of Development for the Fisher College of Business develops and implements short- and long-term plans to secure major gifts from alumni, friends, volunteers and entities in support of the colleges and university's missions, objectives and priorities as set by the unit directors, college dean and development’s senior vice president. Focus of the position is to build a pipeline of major gift prospects for the college in a college culture of constant change with exciting, cutting-edge programs. A person who loves the hunt and enjoys uncovering and building relationships with friends of the university will thrive in this position. The Development team in the Fisher College of Business relies on many strong partnerships with colleagues across campus and takes pride in personal accountability. This collaborative environment encourages and rewards independently motivated individuals who are not easily deterred and have dogged determination. The successful individual in this position will have proven ability to make a large number of cold calls and personal visits and cultivate prospects, moving them along the prospect continuum to eventually secure major gifts.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Development/OSU Foundation</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52988</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:27-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:27-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52988"/>
    <title>Office Associate</title>
    <content>Works as part of the OSU Extension team in Franklin County. The Office Associate provides administrative and program related support for the county Extension Office; provides financial support for the county office, customer service support through contact with the public, and office support for Extension Educators and Program Assistants. The Office Associate also assists with the Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Position Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;25%:&lt;/b&gt;  Administrative/County Operations: Initiates payment of all invoices through appropriate procedures; monitors and tracks appropriated and non-appropriated university funds, reconciles e-reports on a monthly basis, and provides monthly reports to the county extension director and other educators; and prepares and makes deposits, monitors and tracks local account funds. Processes and pays bills; generates reports; submits purchase orders and expenses for payment; maintains and reconciles fiscal operations, both appropriated and non-appropriated, including monthly reports, checking account, registration fees and ledgers, weekly deposits and receipts; and prepares and maintains accounts payable and receivable. Maintains an office supply inventory and orders items as needed; and orders program related supplies as requested by program staff. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;10%&lt;/b&gt;:  Basic office support for all program areas. Maintains electronic and manual record keeping and inventory systems, including office technology and capital equipment; researches, copies and updates files; oversees copiers, printers and postage system, including reading and processing monthly usage; maintains office phone system (i.e. adding new users, setting main greetings, etc.). Assists in preparing for office and program meetings and attends these meetings to take notes and transcribe into minutes as requested; and performs other administrative tasks in support of the office. Oversees scheduling for meeting rooms; and assists in planning and overseeing arrangements for special events, programs and conferences. Maintains confidentiality of participants and individual records; attends training meetings and staff meetings as required. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;10%:&lt;/b&gt;  Technology and Word Processing. Produces routine to complex technical documents; proofs and edits correspondences; assists in formatting newsletters, presentations, posters, and other program materials; modifies and maintains the county web site, including staying current with OSU/OSUE web design software; assists staff in following and integrating OSU/OSUE branding standards; and creates databases and enters a variety of data on spreadsheets and web-based platforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;5%:&lt;/b&gt;  Customer Service: Answers telephones and serves as the primary first contact for on-site visitors; opens, sorts and distributes daily mail, fax, and other communications; operates office equipment and troubleshoots when necessary; maintains a high level of professionalism at all times and protects confidential information.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Franklin County</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>52971</id>
    <published>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</published>
    <updated>2014-02-22T01:04:12-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.jobsatosu.com/postings/52971"/>
    <title>Fiscal Associate</title>
    <content>The Fiscal Associate performs compliance review for all purchases against University and department policies, guidelines and procedures, including purchase orders, travel requests, reimbursements and PCard expenditures for Advancement; serves as a delegated buyer; assists with developing and implementing internal policies and controls; provides high level of customer service to the staff ensuring processing is timely, efficient, and accurate; assists with developing and presenting fiscal training workshops for department staff; reconciles payroll expenditures and performs other duties as assigned.</content>
    <author>
      <name>Development/OSU Foundation</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
